Welcome to the night, the car is laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secret sun fall
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
Feel the romance in every arcane world
Hold on one second, I am putting
videos. Canva. Fuck.
This will be so worth it though.
I just want to let you okay one more time projects
Oh, okay at the project okay explore save video
Hi guys, I'm sorry
You hear me hold on. Hi interesting. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm trying to
Be this dumb video. I thought I had it ready to go. I'm sorry
I'm ready to go crotch cam. Okay. That was the armpit. I know I know
Here
How do you know, I mean, how do you know I was Mr. McAfee? I was Mr. McAfee ground control the major town
I know I'm sorry guys. How are you doing?
Okay, the waste of time goodbye. Well, goodbye to you. I mean, I'm sorry. I'm trying to do it. Okay, so guys
Okay, fuck Elf
Do I have another song for you?
It's ready. Yeah, it's ready. I wanted to put this one to the video, but
It didn't work, okay, so I'm gonna just put it regular in regular
I need to do it through here. Okay, so I need to go streamers.
Okay, now put through the audio, and that'll be it. We're going to take out the open-tilted
back, okay, so it's fine. Okay, I'm in, I'm in, I'm in, okay.
Watch this, we'll just take a second, okay, there.
Then I go media, and I go music, and music, and it's called okay, it's called crazy.
Okay, so it's ready to go
Are you here
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos
Okay
And it should be ready
Ready guys, okay, it's time to go
Miri the new song
and stripes flash flash turning into tacos with the cider with lash fish guts on the
mic got salsa in my eye i'm dancing on the table like conspiracies don't die
How'd you like it? What do you think?
Oh
Do I yeah, so yeah, we gotta play that again soon very soon. Oh
Did you see do you guys hear it or did not hear it no one's like laughing hysterically like oh my god, I'm so good
Do I have a fever?
Right content. I don't understand
It was great. Okay. Good someone liked it. We have one person like this one person. That's fine with me
Better than know it
Okay
Well, you can't buy my fucking lens of my glasses
Okay, dang it
Okay, you like you too. Okay good my fucking glasses
I have one fucking lens now. There's six six man. Well
Yeah, I'll be perfect right
I don't think you know what intuition means.
I guess Scum is history of being a self once again.
How's that?
I don't know.
I don't know, I saw Scum recently thinking
that he was G.G. Allen, something like that.
I don't know.
I hope you're okay, Scum.
Life is a fever dream, huh?
that I heard you and then please it okay hi guys well I really have followers I
have leaders I have leaders Patrick what are you doing outside tonight
You're outside of what?
I'm not Patrick. I'm just Pat Patrick. Thank you. We can't care. What are they doing outside?
What are they doing earlier? Was I outside of what? Yeah, I'm into my
family dinner
Thanks, I don't I just do this
Okay, you love it. Thank you
That's that I heard you say it come I don't know I heard you say it I don't know you're saying I don't know what intuition
I heard you
Am I gonna call the cops that no, I don't I'm not a cop caller really I mean if I needed to it I
was like kid
not really
Yeah, we had a little family stuff. I think that's a part of lemonade
That's good
Me's Liz you were huge but yes, so I got away from you know beat up pages in the song again
God he made that song God was in that song
careless Kate was in the song
Like
Sometimes from it was hard mr. Big Pies made it a few times to you guys
How did I know like the story though? I was like oh mr. Big Pies won't be it's new exact
Oh, he won't leave it. Yeah, he's muted out like it's so funny
They got you know, yeah, it's just
I think I got everybody's, I don't know if it spunk you,
I don't know if it came out,
I'm gonna have to write another couple of songs.
I was trying like guys I was late tonight
cause I was trying to put it to like music.
How fucking difficult is, I mean, it's like,
versus like generating, I mean,
and then it's trying to, it's trying to like,
it's always learning, yeah.
Yeah, I don't know. I tried to make it make music videos. It didn't quite quite work
That's came for like, you know a subscription don't know you should go on the
Yeah
Do we see people soon you guys hear the other song too skimless. Are you okay? What's wrong?
Everyone said yeah, it is it's constantly in and it knows what everyone's saying. I am I'm enjoying redondo
What's wrong with someone's wrong? Why are you, why are you, why are you, why are you, uh,
spurging out or spur, that's called crashing out, spurging out? But I don't know, what is he doing,
guys? He seems like he's upset. I've been there, I guess, that's he's upset.
So I'm having like a lot of fun with these AI songs. So, I mean, I'll figure out the video stuff.
But at least have a month full of songs
monthful of songs
Me right mate it's kind of the same weird stuff again. Well, it's nothing else with me
Happens sometimes. It's okay. It's all it's all like have a good vibe like not
You're doing a lot of thinking in regards. Yeah, I wonder what would be in terms of regarding the ultimate question
What is the universal good? I
Think universal good is life
It's like I think it is an emphasis towards life and compassion and
You know caring and like you know non-harm
Your powers are wearing down your drugs almost done. You can type you can't type in the taps anymore
It hits the seat will scroll again 29 people in chat. That's awesome
Wow, and there's a lot of people even when I just started the live there wasn't any people in it yet
There's people it was like, you know, I'm really excited that
People are here. Of course, you know
That asshole
He's trying to form on me having me take down my content and stuff like that. So I do have to do occasionally
I can never answer questions reason what humans say. Yeah, I mean humans program AI
It's always gonna be the humans programming AI, but we're humans programs too, right?
So we're like who's program who's the ultimate programmer? That's the question right also is programming solve programming
Everything like I don't know what's not programming. It's all
Everything is programming.
Yeah, I can't answer any question except based on what it's not gonna logic and think oh, okay
Well, it's not gonna know certain thing you're gonna five a bit think of see you're gonna need to retire from the corporate world business in life with section surgery
They're broken to cut your losses and short there. Okay. Well, you know, there's always options
It's like we live in just a culture that's like oh, so this is like what you're means to be happy. This is like wealth, right?
And I said, nothing's really happy.
There's almost people that are just as happy as a billionaire.
There are fishermen as happy as the CEO of a magazine.
I mean, so it's like,
if you are not supposed to know everything, huh?
I think we also are trying to,
like at least we're gonna try to,
like we're gonna try to, we can't, right?
But we're the, something that keeps us going to learn,
to learn more, like we won't stop like,
oh, okay, we know everything.
Now, or else we wouldn't get in space,
We focus them because we think we know we're just like keep going to different topics
We need to like stay on the same topic sometimes right you want to do an online gynecology. It sounds like interesting
you know
You know a lot of people are just are showing their vaginas already says online
But you know we just needed people that know how to know what's going on with them, right?
We're gonna need a lot of vagina doctors in the future guys
Yes, always see you know always seeking is the curiosity like Alice is not like oh, I know everything she's like
I don't know what the fuck is going on Stephanie. Just I got a file. Oh, yeah, there you go. No, you're talking to them. I'm sorry
Okay, well low risk high rewards. That's a yeah, that's what the ultimate goal is right?
We want that's what we want. We want like a low risk and high high. I pay out, right?
The thing that's most rare kind. I wonder if AI knows of what it does and know. Does anybody know what they don't know?
That's part of the you don't know what you don't know because it's like you don't know it
So you don't even know what you don't know you don't know or you don't know you don't know you don't care
It goes on forever
Yeah
I wonder what I didn't know what about. Oh, yeah, I rose the and I went down that rabbit hole already
I mean sick reason of the you go down that rabbit hole. You just keep continuing staying over and over the unknown unknown
Is this it I'm gonna take a job working for a water plan of the city
Okay, get one of those. Um, you're gonna make sure you're past your drug test or get a whizzenator
Is they fake penis thing with a bladder bag?
Comic could come along any day, right?
The bus if you remember a mean girls that popular girl got hit by a bus like right at the end right?
Just a thought right?
Knows what will happen
Possibilities are endless
Here you go, no matter how, yeah, it works.
Oh, there you go.
Yeah, large language model, yeah.
It's a bunch of words, it's like,
predicts the next word to be said pretty much, right?
Yes, and the Tim Hortons only hires non-whites,
non-Christian, they're assuming against white.
Isn't Tim Hortons like in Canada or something?
Is it Canadian?
Are you Canadian?
Eh, I'm Canadian, eh.
Okay.
Oh no, you're doing the Johnny Depp stuff, spunky, spunky, well you don't have to tell her, she'll smell it, she'll smell it.
Okay, do queer at the peer streams until 5,000, queer at the peer, well what does that entail?
Because a lot of people at the peer do not want to be hit on.
Some of them don't have a sense of humor.
If you're a romantic type, Boyle, yeah.
He's very romantic with the kuban bed.
So let me have a look at my channel.
So how does it look guys? I put up a new banner. I know I didn't put up a new banner same been okay
Well, the banner looks fine. Oh look finally the banner. Let's find
Take you terror channel, right?
Okay
Membership thank you. Eldo Eldo bought some memberships earlier in the stream and
Careless cake got one who else got one someone else
Gish maybe and
Very cool
Did I so I have a I think I'm at 96 or 97 let's get to 100 members guys. I'll be so excited
We have over 100 members videos 10 custom emojis loyalty badges that would you change through the months photos status updates?
I will do a
Two hours a week of members only any one of the days I will do
See it's all the way till the year he is the color changing. Yeah, it has the only good thing. Oh, that's sweet
Well, that's our good very good things
But yeah members you get to remember shout out. I
Mean just so many awesome awesome things. Okay, so many wonderful
incredible things, okay
So
Having a look let's see. I'm no I'm the number one thing on my stream. Okay. Okay. What up menu for 20, okay
You know, okay
Oh, so I just shut it down
It's a deep subject yes
Let's see.
Well, good.
You can have a conversation with your cat.
Okay.
Oh, she's a wonderful woman.
Weird.
Your cat's a woman.
Okay.
So, are you ready for the other,
do you want to hear the other song again?
It is 10.28 p.m. Oh, it's already 10.30 p.m.
I think I'm late.
Tell you and you heard him try to take out Wiener on site.
He's down.
Who did who did that?
That was
to 82 times, right?
82 times.
He tried to take out his Wiener.
I don't know if he tried to take out his Wiener.
He just touched it.
It's 128.
Okay.
Well, it's time to play the other song. This one's called Crazy, I think. Let me see. I was not supposed to call...
Enjoy Madness. This is called Madness. Which one is it?
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos in the stream be the callin and slurring words starting up the scene talking all that trash
Then she flips rage Queen mad at me girl, please the show runs on caffeine
Sikes twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurs flying left and right we cut the feed no shame
But the chats on fire can't tame this flame. This ain't your mama's podcast. This a runaway train
Welcome to the madness buckle up tight boob flashing on cam chat losing their minds
in the chat but she ain't got time for a dude like that diamond flirting hard let the girls
react it's a freak show party no filter all facts yo all facts yo yo michael drops a line
gong not tonight alex tried to joke boom sent into the night panel looking sideways someone's
got to fight producers on mute praying this don't spike diamonds feeling spicy shirt slipping down
Oops, she says we're the wink, that's the whole show
Sides half asleep but still cracking jokes
Slurred out wisdom with a bourbon so glow
No rules, just rolls, we pretend to play one
Enjoy the ride
Welcome to the bandit
Epic, that is like, whoa.
Amazing.
Yup, it's fire callus booty shakes, right?
Oh my gosh.
Take the job.
So what's the next one gonna be?
I'm gonna be, let me see.
How's the book coming along?
The book is, we got fucking drawings for days.
Now we fucking got lyrics.
I've got people contributing, I've got famous trolls already and dying to have an interview
and you contributor, guys, get stuff in the works, okay, I can take transcripts of my
show, summaries, I mean it's like content, I have thousands and thousands of hours,
I think thousands of hours, I have hundreds of shows, thousands of hours, it is good.
It'll be one of those books you press a button up play this down. It'll be like probably just like, you know
It's like a
Like I just have pictures the one I have words. I just have pictures of that. I showed them the power and
Bruise them around from the start bossing around. Oh the audiobook had the AI songs, too. Yeah
Guys, it'll be a whole fucking thing. Yeah
You're the yeah
I'm getting drunk on stuff saying tracking drugs or tracking jokes when I'm falling asleep.
Do you like it guys?
That's pretty cool.
I love the personalization.
I'm going to do one for...
Yeah, you gotta have patience. I would say that's one of the biggest in us. Like Capricorns have a lot of patience. Hi. Hi. How are you?
You me
Yeah, you have to have a lot of patience you have to have
Little bit of maybe a little bit crazy, I think you have to be a little bit crazy because
The hang I don't know
To be able to like you know deal with it. I don't know
That'd be a little bit crazy a little bit
Not too crazy though crazy like a fox, right?
Okay, so I'm having some good conversations
Well, I'll make another one while we're doing the show.
I'll make another one, you know,
but I'm gonna like ask, you know,
as soon as the beat it comes in, I'll play her,
I'll play her the,
I'm gonna say, so let me think, so high page.
Oh pages here, so maybe maybe it's time to play the song again soon. You guys ready to hear it again soon
I'll play it played in a few minutes. So I'm gonna write another song. Okay, so this one who will be in this song? Okay
Nick
Nick Johnson he gets a mention. Okay. I think I'll just I can just have like
Five people in it. Okay, so just this next one will be Nick. It will be
Crystal crystal Marie
It will be, um, well, uh, Eldo, it will have Spunky, okay, Spunky, uh, one more person,
Who else?
Oh, how about Joker?
Okay, I'll do six people.
Joker and who else?
One more person.
More person, who else?
Somebody iconic.
Iconic chatter.
Joe.
I think I'm done, Joe.
I got Summer.
Hold on, somebody iconic.
Mini Manson?
Let's do Mini Manson.
Okay, so here's how to do it guys.
Here's how you do a song.
And I'll just, I'll walk you through the process.
I'll show you how I do it,
and then you can like do it your own way,
but you'll see how easy it is.
Okay, so all you have to do is go to chatGPT.
It's very, it's free, you know?
I don't know if you use it, but.
Yeah, GPT, okay.
All right, let's go to chatGPT website.
Okay, so I'm not going to tell you exactly what I type
But I'll tell you you just go to chat GPT and you go create an AI create lears for an AI song
About and then I can say
Share information like the name of your show or whatever or like the name you'd like the song. Okay
Okay, many stages talk about certain things
And then you say, what's the panel's about?
Kind of like think of what it might run with.
OK.
Okay
And then you say what about the person you say what the person's name and what they did like it's not something that they did
Okay, um, okay, spunky
Okay
Okay, and
Any man sin sings more
lose and
shows and
says
Okay, so I just wrote like a long thing, okay.
So it's, okay, so now I've, okay, so I've written along.
It says, sure, okay, so here's the Wilder.
So now it's written,
The Psyche Awakens, The Tarot Show Song.
Okay, it says it's a psychedelic rock comedy hip-hop.
Okay, so I'm not gonna tell you what it says yet.
I'm just gonna plug it into the generator,
and then I'll, oh wow, it's a long song.
Okay, okay, and then I'm gonna, you know.
I'll make it. Still creating the song. Okay. So, okay. So, oh, okay. Oh, wow, this looks,
okay, this looks funny. Okay, this looks funny. You got excited? So, this will be really cool.
This will be really cool. Okay. There we go. Okay. Now, you just got to copy it. Okay. So,
This one you can go but it's like in order to like share it with you know
It's like share it with people you need to have the upgrade, but it's free just to make the song. Okay
So
Hey, I music generator online, okay, you plug it in there
And then it says, you know, it says psychedelic rock or something, okay, so
Okay, so psychedelic rock.
You push.
See, okay, it's really fast.
You just put, okay, so it says genre
and it will say like psychedelic,
what does it say?
I mean, psychedelic rock, okay?
There's a psychedelic rock.
Remember what else it said?
Psychedelic rock and comedy hip-hop, okay?
So hip-hop, okay, so then I have hip-hop too.
Hip-hop, okay. I don't see comedy, but
Okay
That's good enough
Okay, so now it's creating the song
Okay, now it's made it. No, it's generating now. Is that crazy? Am I at least writing a lyric? No, I'm telling like
Things about people and it kind of writes lyrics for me, you know, it's like will
It'll say things I should send me the one rapper. Okay, but I'll play the new it's a new one
Here's the new uh, this is one of the newer ones. This one is just made. Okay, this one's called
crazy
on the table like conspiracy don't die
Okay, how is that one? You like that one? Okay, so now let me it's still creating the new songs, okay
That was funny oh shit, that was good. Yeah, I like it. It's kind of funny
Okay, so now I have the new song, ready for the new song?
Okay, this week it premiered the new song now,
I think it's almost ready.
Okay, it says download mp3.
Okay.
Okay, so all I have to do is put this now in the,
I have to delete something and put something else in.
Okay, hold on a second, I'll delete this.
I'm just a fish taco in a world on fire.
I don't know.
Okay, hold on.
Here, okay, I'll turn up the volume too.
There we go, okay.
More music, okay.
Then I add music, and.
Okay, guys, so already, it's already, already, already.
So this is the premiere of,
oh, hold on, I have to do it here.
Okay, hold on a second.
Okay.
You need to see something here.
Play this immediately.
That would be cute.
Here, let's see how this one is.
I hope this one will be good too.
This is a psychedelic.
Okay, so let's go.
more music, music.
Didn't download it.
Sorry, guys, technical difficulties, of course.
OK.
You may not have been ready to go.
OK, here we go.
My songs.
P3.
Okay, it worked. Okay
So here's the new song guys
Ready how exciting I'd love a new familiar
Okay ready
Where the tarot flies
Psyche awakens, tune in tight
Panels get wild like Friday night
Cards on fire, drama ignite
Crystals flying, she's taking flight
Mixing costume, eyes are red
Bong in hand and nothing said
Tilly drops a quote, half baked and weird
Then laughs like a wizard with a twisted beard
This ain't your grandma's tarot show
Where the cards fall fast
And the weirdness flows
We stir the pot, we break the mold
It's Psyche Awakens
Control!
Eldos driving, CB blaring, truck stop wisdom, always daring, he calls in loud, kicks up
the mess, starts a feud in the comments, non-stop stress.
Bunky jumps in with a wink and a punch, sharp like tarot, sweet like sun, rolls her eyes,
sips her tea, brings the heat with sarcasm, glee.
Down in the dark with a mole rat's creep, many men send scenes right to sleep, he howls
to the moon with a bluesy sting, tarot cards dance and the spirits sing.
Jokers here with a smirk so sly, draws pages, faces with a sparkle eye.
Flirts like crazy, page just grits, she rolls the dice and the chaos begins.
30,000 feet dropping hot takes can't be beat one minutes in next minute war drops a truth bomb then ask for more
Starts a feud in the comments, non-stress
Comments, nonstop stress, sweet spunky jumps in with a wink and a pun, sharp like tarot, sweet like sun, rolls her eyes, sips her tea, brings the heat with sarcasm, Glee.
Yeah
That was good, oh my god
That pretty good I'm impressed
Whoa, how does it how does it know so I get knows this listen to the show it seems like it
It's familiar and it's like if you didn't hear it, it was like Crystal at 3000 feet because you know she's like she's like a pilot
I don't know that there's very obscure references. You want more? I know it's gonna be so much fun
I like that is so funny
Uh
Because i'm not like the ai doesn't know but it does know it doesn't but it does you know
It's just like in the right
Just saying all the right things, you know, I don't know
whoa
Yeah, I get it key words, right? But oh my gosh summer. Oh my gosh. Yeah
Very much fun. Let's do it. We can do another one. I'll just I'm listening to what we can the song suck ass
It's okay juice hall. It's okay. You know, it's fine. Where's your song? Where's the juice hall song?
I didn't hear that, huh? What are you doing? Are you sitting in here having a show? It was like a 38 people
I don't have any fun except for you. No
Okay juice hall
And draw you if you're not here. Okay, so
Big me say yeah, okay, so we're not
We do a big night. You can do a big nation memorial song. Oh my gosh. We have so many things to do
You'd like to answer the mystery. Okay. Yeah, I know but that's that's my song. I mean that's a mystery
It's my song. Okay. Wait, okay. Let me see
We see
Hmm
It's just so much fun, but we'll do some more later of that. I guess you guys are tired of it
I'll continue with this book. I was reading until you actually have shots of death. Oh, no
With that with what syringes?
Are you gonna adopt down now
Okay, recreate the mystery as a death metal song. Yeah, I can actually I can
You want me to I don't know if I should
I need I need the lyrics can someone type out the lyrics dance to the mystery
Welcome to the night. Yep. Okay summer was the song. Okay, so the next song will have summer in it
We'll do this like we'll do it with all people in the chat. You know, so
okay, so
Okay, we got summer okay, so we'll just do five people because six people makes this are repeating stuff
It got kind of weird it so we have summer
Okay
Okay, who else you want Canada dry wants to be in there
Okay, who else
Okay
Canada's right to drinks just cash ones in place the Canada's also a place but not Canada dry
Make a song about okay, hold on put Oliver in the song Oliver will be in a song
Okay
Make a song about summer being a country baddie, okay?
So Summer, Oliver, who else would be in this song?
Who wants to be in it?
Anybody?
Shout out.
Or a good idea if you should be in it.
I think Vita is pretty iconic.
I think Vita should be in the song.
I'll put Vita in this next one too.
Who else?
9420, okay, 9420.
Okay, and Trina and Kristina, okay.
Okay, my name's 420, I just can't,
I'll put you in the next one, it's just like,
it's just like, I always have the females,
a females of the show, so I think.
Hot mess crew, yeah, hot mess, okay.
Okay, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh.
Okay, okay, Kristina.
Okay, and
Okay, all right, okay, so I you know, I don't write I
Could not write like a funny song. It was just not be funny
You know the AI seems to know how to do it. You know, it's just so
I'll let I'll just go through the chat GPT for the
For the
Crafty I give the ideas, you know, right? I get the ideas of it like tell them like something about everybody
but
They come up with things the funny twist to it. It's just funny or that I don't know it
You know kind of I don't know. Let me see. Let me see. So it goes chat EPT
Okay
Okay, well, I'm gonna surprise you guys with this one. So just talk amongst yourself for a second
Mm-hmm
up some pages there too, just for good measure.
Okay, so I've never written a song
Basically, I hope wait, I don't know if it okay, so okay, so now it's okay, so it's gonna be a okay
It's gonna be oh, I guess what I called it called it late night angels and guys they're called psyche's angels
I didn't say the angels thing. Okay, they called it late night angel. Okay, so
That's pretty cool
Okay. Okay. Let me know if you'd like to adapt a specific genre. Let me see. So what did it say? It said it's in a
Dreamy Viby Acoustic Ballad. Okay. It's an acoustic ballad. Okay.
We'll see how this one goes. Dreamy Acoustic Ballad. A ballad. Wow.
This guy's is gonna be funny.
This is gonna be so much fun.
And again, almost have an album of the whole thing, okay?
So there you go.
Okay, copy.
Oh shit.
Okay, there you go.
This is too funny.
Okay, so then I copy that, put it into the AI.
It's the lyrics there, okay.
Recommend it as a ballad.
Oh, I think this will be funny, okay.
Ballad.
Angels
Okay, so the acoustic
See if you valid I see traditional
Nice even search for
Ballot what is acoustic something right? I just say acoustic
Ballot
I'll just do it. I'll just do a blue bluegrass. It's that's like Kentucky here. Okay. It's just like that
there's something there like a
Persian to old Russian Oh
Arabic I'll put Arabic too. I'll do Arabic and the Kentucky in there too. We'll just see how it sounds
I mean, it might be just ridiculous. We do know we'll just test it out
Okay
No
Are these free? I signed up for this website. It gave me like a thousand credits. It's how it's like
It does have a free tier, but in order for me to put like to download the
The thing you know like the bluegrass. Oh, well too late. It's mixed with arabic. Maybe we'll create a special combination. Who knows?
Hi charisma. Hi, he man. I
Don't know. I mean, it's like, you know, I could have said like I could have felt like
Saskatchewan folk? I'm not sure. Okay, it is working on it.
Let me clear out my, let me see, clear some of this out.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry,
Okay, so my sound effects, so I have a few other ones. Let me see
This one sounds like crystal a little bit
Loud
hey how do you like the uh you like the new uh that's cool do you like the new uh emojis members
members is uh i have a whole new bag of tricks i know guys i just i feel like i don't know it was
you know what it really was when i got canva like canva has really tried the gong sound effect
That's like your favorite sound.
Okay, so it's ready.
Okay, let's see.
Down the wave.
Down the MP3.
Okay, so then I go to stream yard.
That's a gong.
I mean, I'll try to find another one.
Okay, ready this very quickly. Oh shit
I'm still doing this one, shit.
Yeah
Sorry hey princess Lila
Yeah, it's like a little bit slow, I guess because it's like
Take a little bit to download it to
Get the country the bluegrass mess mess them up down the way file come on slow
Hey, Marcy. Oh, I should put Marcy in this one. Okay, I'll put Marcy in this one.
I mean, to save it, download it.
Where is the angel?
I should say angel somewhere.
show hidden files.
Okay, I'm sorry. I'm trying to try to like get this to download
Recent come on
Sorry guys, so what are you doing guys? I'm sorry. I'm trying to you know, it's not very fun. I'm still getting at the
Okay, audio
It's not working. Okay, well, unless it's like any of the same thing 46 megabytes
How many have I done? That keeps on creating.
Okay, I think I figured it out. I think I figured it out. I think I figured it out. Okay. Uh-oh. Okay. Hold on. I figured it out.
I'm sorry. I know this is a pain. This is a pain in the ass.
Oh my god.
Clearly the stream air is crashing.
Here we go.
Okay guys at worst finally got it finally fine finally okay finally it worked finally
Finally I'm sorry that took forever
Okay, here we go
Summer walks in like a storm with flame
Tattooed fire and a golden name
Tough as steel but soft inside
She'll break your walls with just her smile
Christine's eyes, they see it all
With wisdom deep like an endless fall
And fuzzy by her side
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
Oh, Marcy, come on.
Please, the BTK stuff, I mean, come on.
That was cute.
I think that was just a cute song.
Katrina, Peyton, Bita.
Oh, yeah, it was like a little cute little song.
Satan is alive and well.
See, you've always thought, I'm going, yeah,
they're all saved.
But that was a cute song, it was cute.
Upload them as sure. Yeah, it was about how it's heartwarming. It was
We're gonna do the I'm sorry to take a little bit of time to put on it's trying to figure out how to do it on right
I'm getting good. I'm getting better at this. So
It was heartwarming
cool and so guys
Yeah, we're all friends. Yeah, we're all friends. Oh
Eleanor Eleanor's back there
Hi, hi Lenore. Hi, come here
What?
You love this song awesome
It was a little bit I mean, I know it's a little bit sweet, you know, it's like I mean I was touched I was touched you didn't do you?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, so I think that was cute
Does that mean it? Yeah. Yeah, you have to write about their very nice. Let's see. Let's write nice. You support each other, right?
Some people are going to yeah, well
Yeah, better send me the song before you forget. Oh, yeah, so I'll put them on I'll put it on this for you
I'll put I'll get them uploaded to like a
We'll make a little page of my songs. It's so cute. I think I do have to maybe
Just check
Maybe I was Mars. I don't know. Oh, but it's okay. I don't see those. He's crying. She's someone that's chattis bothering her. I'm not sure
Hmm
Oh, I do have a donut left. Look at I
Embrace the chocolate one
Hmm
I know maybe this song it will come out looking like one of them probably right
So win-win
Hmm, oh, I'm the birth of a tree
So come out with a picket sign, maybe welcome out with a picket sign with a red-haired,
red-dead-haired activism.
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm a slurper. I do slurp
Okay
So let's see
I want to continue reading that book. I think we're almost done with that book how to control
a codependent, which is, you know, it's a satire,
because we don't really want to,
of course we don't want to control anybody.
It's about how certain people think,
like these certain talks,
these certain talks, their personality types,
think when they are dealing with other people,
and since we want to protect ourselves,
it's good to know how they might view us, okay?
So, let's explore library.
Okay, library.
Okay.
Okay, so,
where are we in the book?
Okay.
So, this one says alienate.
Okay, here's the panel. If you want to go to the other one, I'll come with the panel. Here you go.
Just music tonight.
says you must cut it says alienate says you must cut off your codependence from their relationship with non abusers if they
Have any sources of happiness away from you block them from accessing him
Any competition for their attention will destroy the illusion you are weaving it must be remembered that your codependent may in fact be bright
intelligent congenial and fun don't allow them to be reminded of all their positive attributes by anyone else
If you allow the co-dependent interactions with positive friends or family members, they will be given praise and approval.
This cannot be allowed. They must not be allowed to have any source of validation outside of you.
You have to establish a monopoly on praise, validation, and approval.
Then you can control how much or how little they get. That is what hooks them to you.
The purpose of this is to ensure that your attacks on their self-deceive stick.
If you tell your codependent that they can't sing or dance well,
you need that criticism to be taken to heart.
If they have friends who contradict the narrative you're weaving, you'll lose control.
You can't mold the lump of clay into the form you desire if other people try to put their hands in your clay.
Tolerate no contradictions, say things like nobody knows the real you like I do, establish
yourself as a sole authority in their lives, undermine the level of intimacy or closeness
they have with others, with comments which imply that you alone know the soul of your
codependent.
Given the little time you'll find that you won't have to hold the leash so tight your codependent will withdraw voluntarily from everyone else
This occurs gradually the more you devalue your codependent the lower their self self-esteem goes
You must cultivate their insecurities these insecurities will become a prison as they interact less and less with the world outside
Make them feel rejected by the world tell them how nobody understands them like you do
The more you come to define who your codependent is, the more shame you can introduce.
As they adopt the self-image you impose as their real self, the more they will fear exposure.
Make them constantly aware that you know alone who they really are.
Just as you wear a mask to obscure your real self and control those you have learned into
your life, you must insist that those you control wear masks as well.
need to decide who and what they are and hold them to it. Just as they don't know you are a mask,
they won't be aware that they have one too. Do not address the integrated well-adjusted person
they were when you met. Instead, address your codependent as a flawed and shamefully inadequate
person not worthy of love. Talk to the mask you've created for your victim and they'll respond to that
When you're alienating your codependent from friends and family, you have to come to ensure
that they've never witnessed inactive abuse.
Do not let anyone see you devaluing your victim.
Every person in your victim's life needs to be on a pedestal.
Don't restrict your abuse cycle to those you have isolated.
Everyone is a potential victim.
Every person in your life in the life of your victim needs to be idealized
This will charm them disarm them and if you're patient you can use your victims family and friends as proxy abusers
through the tactics of triangulation
For example flirting with a sibling of your victim if done tactfully and light-hearted enough to give you semblance of plausible
Deniability will cause infighting tap into sibling rivalries when you can same goes for their friends
You want their friends to like you more than them
This will cause your victim to further distance themselves from those family members and friends
who seem to be competing for your attention.
Always remember the cardinal rule of alienation.
Charm to disarm.
If you charm all those you wish to cut out
of your victim's life, they won't see you as an abuser,
but will rather take your side
and even encourage your victim to stay with you.
If your victim should run to one of those you have charmed,
they'll invalidate your victim and send them back to you.
If anything, you'll be seen as a martyr,
which is a particularly powerful role to be in.
If you can't be seen as a victim of an irrational person,
to a note. You'll be above reproach. No one will know you're a narcissistic abuser controlling
an enslaved codependent. Wow. Okay, the next one, open old wounds.
The nice thing about emotional abuse is that it leaves no visible scars.
Emotional pain is processed in the same part of your brain as physical pain.
This means that you can control your codependent with mental and psychological torture just
as effectively as punching, whipping, slapping, and other overt methods of dominating their
will.
Even verbal abuse is a rarely good idea because if you're caught on videotape or overheard,
the mask can slip.
These forms of emotional abuse you should use are those which are covert subtle and hard to detect
You can do more damage when you have plausible deniability. Think of this approach by
Death by a thousand cuts rather than totally going OJ Simpson on your victims
You'll know you've succeeded when your target is left looking like a self pitting basket case rather than a victim of abuse
Which they are that way
can get in their head is by tearing down their protective boundaries. Most codependent are
boundary deficient, which makes it easy. To find all the little wounds and emotional scars of
your victim, you simply need to get them to open up and reveal themselves. They'll show you their
scars once they trust you. You gain their trust by showing them your own scars. Usually you'll
have to make them up. Invent past traumas, which will trigger the most empathy. If your target was
abused as a child or a teen, then you need to must be a victim of abuse. If your target was poor
Ego boundaries must be destroyed, insist that there are no secrets between you.
It doesn't matter what their secrets are, all that matters is that you can get them
to reveal their innermost thoughts.
You want to psychologically strip your targets bare.
This will cause them to feel like you care more than you do.
Using interrogation techniques probe the same areas for many different angles.
Play good cop, bad cop with them, but don't show your bad cop side.
Without being too aggressive, make every conversation a pissing contest.
Mirror their every achievement, experience and feeling.
You need to one up every significant life experience they share with you.
This has a two-fold purpose.
One, you're showing them how you're exactly the same as they are.
And two, you're subtly invalidating them on a deep level.
You need to emerge as a dominant one without being too obvious about it.
Let them come to their own realizations about your superiority.
Keep a list in your mind of all significant events in your life.
You'll be using music again some later.
For example, if your codependent was
Cheated on in the past then you'll want to play it on that insecurity later
For example now, I know why you were cheated on you're too prude
This allows you to to layer a new pain on top of old traumas
Simple attacks like that will inflict a lot of pain
But won't leave any marks and won't even require you to raise your voice
This is the key when you're calm and impenetrable while you're having an emotional breakdown
The disparity will only make while they're having emotional breakdown the disparity will only make them look and feel crazy
Crazy making is the name of the game you need to make them
You need them to feel crazy. This will make it easier to put the blame on them
for their own victimization.
At the beginning of your relationship,
when you're idealizing your victim,
they will feel invincible.
You'll lift them up and make them believe
that they're the person you are elevating.
They will, for that short time,
actually think highly of themselves.
Codependence craves to kind of praise and attention
on a deep, deep level.
Therefore, they will be susceptible to your charm,
more susceptible to your charm than any other time.
Don't rush to tear them down.
Give them time to reveal their secrets, their fears,
and anything they're ashamed of.
The past trauma every past trauma is a doorway to their pain sensors
These are the buttons and levers you will use to dominate and control them once you pull them off their pedestal ouch
Nice isn't that scary that people will think this way
But it's scary, right? Let's keep them boxed in don't allow your coup dependent to express individuality deny them spontaneity
Keep them boxed into the parameters which define them when you first met, don't allow them to grow.
Anytime something spontaneous arises that transgresses these boundaries, cast size them, ridicule them, and above all invalidate whatever it is they're doing.
For example, if your codependent was a horror movie fanatic when you met, don't tolerate romantic comedies later.
If you can find your codependent deviating from your established mold, undermine them whenever they're getting into, use phrases like,
Seriously? Why are you reading? You never read. You don't have to be mean or restrictive. You just
have to be consistent in your criticism. Your job is to police their thoughts and thereby limit
their options, which makes a slave a slave is their lack of options. You must restrict their range
of options in order to control them. If you allow your codependent to take on a new hobby or past
time, you risk them having access to self-esteem-boosting experiences. You don't want them to develop
Keep them moldy, stagnant, keep them complacent, encourage slothfulness, do not permit your
codependent to stay in shape and dress well. You want them to lose self-confidence and nothing
will arouse self-confidence like the self-consciousness which comes from weight gain, poor eating habits,
and lack of loss of social ability. Isolated people will tend to become increasingly asocial.
When you've helped them into a lifestyle which makes them feel unattractive, they'll be more dependent on you for attention.
Consider this an act of assisted social sue, you know, unaliving.
When you're in the role of sole supplier, you can withdraw your attention at any time.
This dynamic gives you power.
This is a book about you know, how narcissists operate with you know, they're dealing with codependent people and it's you know
It's for everyone to think about the mode the mold you create for them
We'll become a prison cell and you'll be their warden
You can then fill them with self doubt and they'll cling to you people are supposed to change over time
It's human nature when you prevent someone from growing and changing you are essentially killing them from the inside out
It's called soul murder. We have cycled their souls expression. You will own their body and mind Wow
You must eliminate their soul their self-esteem and replace that with pseudo self-esteem which is dependent on your approval
Make them beg for approval and always hold the thread of retracting it over their heads
Make them aware of how fragile they are and how flippantly and easily you could reject them
Abuse people will always seek out other abusers because their need for validation, combined
with their low self-esteem, requires it.
The longer you confine your victim within the box, the less pride they will have.
They will not stand up to your abuse.
In fact, they will self-abuse and engage in risky behaviors with no concern for their
long-term safety.
You may find alcohol or other drugs useful in encouraging their self-abasement.
This will also give you new avenues for guilt-tripping and shaming your codependent.
If you do praise them, do so with a forked tongue.
Remember, flattery should only be used to coerce and control, never to boost their self-esteem.
For example, don't say, you look beautiful, and said, say, that dress I bought you looks great on you.
Remind them that you are the source of everything, including even their source of self-worth.
Better yet, you say something terrible about someone you both know using a comparison as
both compliment and threaten.
For instance, you look way hotter than that lazy pig, Sarah.
I'm glad you aced gracefully.
This sends home the message that if she should gain weight or require wrinkles, you'll reject
her.
It also reinforces that she needs to maintain her looks only for your enjoyment of her body,
not her own sense of self-worth.
Men can control their own on their body language body image as well can be controlled in their body image as well
Everyone has body image issues when men with men's receding hairlines potbellies skinny legs or fear of game
The idea here is to target those areas which are difficult or impossible to change
You'll need to focus on those areas. They have no control over the box
You create is made of insecurity and fear you want to turn the fear of change into a resolve not to change
when they are afraid to change or to try and improve themselves,
your other subtle emotional jabs will hit them harder.
It's one thing to be criticized for something one can change
and can gain self-respect for.
It's quite another to be criticized
for something immutable or unchangeable.
If your codependent is insecure about their lack of education, don't attack them on the point until you've made certain they lack the confidence to get into school.
If you attack too soon, you might elicit them into the desire to prove you wrong, which is what you must avoid at all costs.
Don't allow them to take mold-shattering actions, diminish their expectations by placing them into the box and cutting them off mentally from any hope of seeing beyond it.
Okay, now here's the Flying Monkeys chapter. This says, recruit the proxy abusers.
Their victims will eventually become so narrowly focused on their short-term survival that they will disregard their own needs for security, safety, love, and meaning.
Indeed, instead their happiness will revolve around you and your emotions. They will be relaxed only when you're happy.
The rest of the time, they'll be anxious walking on eggshells and attentive to your every need. This is where you want them.
However, there are those times when you don't have direct access to them.
For instance, in between abuse cycles, they might temporarily be out of your reach.
Perhaps you went too far and chased them out of your control matrix.
This is not a problem as long as you have access to proxy abusers.
Proxy abusers are these individuals you have previously charmed with flattery and detention.
The only reason you should ever give attention or compliments to anyone is so that later you
can call upon them for small favors.
For example, if your girlfriend moves in with her parents because you are excessively controlling,
you might have to admit defeat.
However, if you've already established yourself as a nice guy to her family, then you can
go through them to reach her.
For instance, invite her father to lunch and wear your nice guy mask, act dumbfounded and
play the victim.
and move on to other subjects, make her only a small, small percentage of what you talk about.
This will make it easy for him not to mention you to her. And when he does,
she's such a minor part of it that she feels invalidated, minimized, and on top of it...
Since you've presented as a nice guy who's selflessly concerned about her, she will appear to selfish and unconcerned by contrast.
Win over people in your victim social circle in advance in order to extend your range of control in between the abuse cycles.
This will result in their continued sense of alienation.
Even better, you can exert pressure on them to bring your codependent back to you.
They will be your advocates. They will reinforce your role as a good person. Your ability to reach your codependent anywhere will make you
your power all-encompassing.
Many who have escaped emotional abuse will refer to these proxy abusers as flying monkeys, a
reference to the wicked witch of the West and her wing stimmy-in enforcers.
This is an apt description for what you should seek in your proxies. You want unquestioning servants.
Since you can't drop the mask and control them with fear, you have to rely upon their misperception of you as a genuinely nice person.
If you can't maintain that facade, play the aggressive victim and let your flying monkeys become white knights in your service.
Yikes.
So that's it.
That was the book.
That was the last chapter.
Ended with a bang.
You see if this website is still up.
It's called the Anti-Media Network.
It is...
Not up anymore. So the interesting book though, right?
Like is the accident yeah, I think my connection had a good heart, but you know
Hey, nobody's business ain't nobody's business, but mine and my babe. Oh everyone's sleeping. Oh, I put everyone asleep. I'm sorry
Yeah, well
Michael's actually might have had mental problems
The parents that would allow their child to sleep in the bed with them also seem to have mental problems.
Billie Jean is not my lover. She's just a girl who knows that I am the one, right?
But the kid is not my son.
Okay.
She said I am the one.
Then and then.
Two and then.
In a word.
And then that.
Okay, sorry. That wasn't very good. So how is it? So now I can go to like another one.
I can freeze you like the HKTutor because he's really good too. So I read you about like last
night I was reading about the like the power tools people use but this one's called,
There's one called sitting target.
And there's one called no contact
and there's one called escape.
They're all by the same guy.
I'll look into the no contact.
The no contact will really,
that's the thing, it's like that,
it's like the golden bullet in this narcissism thing.
It's very hard to maintain
because they do these things called hoovers, but.
Let me see.
It says you have little in the way of defenses
Okay, so it says you know
It says, once you do a no contact, once you've given the awareness of the period of abuse
that you have been subjected to will have been substantial and significant, you'll be
exhausted quite possibly having a nervous breakdown.
You'll exhibit the symptoms of PTSD, your confidence will be shot, your self esteem will
be on the floor, your coping mechanisms eroded, your capability for critical thinking eradicated.
You are left in an extremely vulnerable position.
This makes you highly susceptible to the Hoover to draw you back into the dance with the narcissist.
You cannot be blamed for falling for the overture once again.
You have little in the way of defenses and then you face the charm,
the seduction, and the promise of the golden period once again.
The golden period is that happy time or if you're being love-bombed, right?
You can resist this in such a weakened state and accordingly they become
I've sucked back into the narcissist world once again.
That's also why they hoover on holidays,
that when you're emotionally vulnerable,
because that's gonna be more likely to be like,
you're gonna wanna talk to somebody,
you're gonna wanna like, you know, not be alone, right?
They enjoy a brief period of rejoicing as they narcissist rolls out the illusion they've
suckered the victim the first time around before the denigration and devaluation begins
once again.
The cycle will go round and around and around.
Intelligent, independent, self-sufficient, and strong people will fall for the seduction
and the process of devaluation discard in the Hoover.
There is no shame to admitting this because even the most socially adept, emotionally
aware and intuitive individual can be and is ensnared by the narcissist.
We are complete experts in the art of seductive illusion.
We have been created to seduce so we get our fuel.
We have plenty of experience at luring people in with our sugar-coated words and empty promises
If you could not resist us at the very outset before you became drained by us,
what chance would you have when we apply such overtures when we have you in an exhausted and run down state?
Accordingly, the instigation of no contact is very difficult for you
because of the condition you find yourself in when you realize you must deploy no contact.
Yet, your difficulties do not end there.
Not only have you been stripped of the positive resources which would help you maintain no
contact, you will become under repeated and sustained attack from us as we seek to hoover
you.
I will be detailing later in this book what you can expect to happen when you try and implement
no contact.
The campaign that will be launched against you and the various power plays that will
be deployed against you.
Knowing that these are in the pipeline and how they will manifest will prove particularly
You need to know how the narcissist will react once you make the decision to implement no-contact.
Then you must know what is in store for you to allow yourself or any chance of maintaining no-contact in a successful manner.
Very few people implement no-contact in a successful manner the first time.
There are four reasons for this.
There's no link. I'm sorry here. I'll open it.
It says firstly they are not sufficiently strong enough secondly
They're unprepared for just how dangerous the narcissist becomes when no contact begins thirdly
They have not prepared their exit and make elementary errors
I suggest you read getting out how to prepare to leave the narcissist for further advice as you ready yourself for no contact
The fourth reason is the person seeking to implement no contact has not read this book
This book is going to tell you all how the narcissist regards no contact how we react to it
What we will do, what you must do, and most of all, it will allow you to see how deep into this e-twisted and evil mind of a narcissist,
so you need to understand why things happen. As a victim of a narcissist, you will have strong empathic qualities,
and one of those traces of the desire to know, empaths always like to know why things happen.
We, by contrast, have no interest in the wise. It is all about the outcome to us.
and we are not in the slightest bit interested as to why this happens, so long as it does.
The empathic individual, on the other hand, is committed to wanting to know,
needing to understand, and this often proves your downfall.
The narcissist is not a creature of logic, or at least not logic as you know it.
In our world, we see everything as straightforward and making sense.
This is not applicable to the way you regard things.
We will say one thing and a moment later contradict ourselves.
you will point this out to us and we will deny any such contradiction even going to
so far as to deny we first made the statement. To you this is utterly illogical and you cannot
comprehend as to whether we cannot see what we have said or done.
To us, it is a necessary device which allows us to maintain the upper hand with you.
We must assert our control over you, and most importantly, your perplexed reaction to our
contradictory behavior provides us with fuel.
You do not realize this.
You do not understand why this is the case, and you keep striving, and we want you to
know to keep doing this, and we want you to keep doing this.
If you look for an answer which is grounded in the logic of your world, you will never
achieve this.
Instead, all you will do is keep granting us power over you.
You will keep giving us fuel.
You will keep tying yourself in knots, exhausting yourself and becoming ground down as you try
and work out why we do what we do.
You make the same mistakes every time.
You try and analyze our behavior through your viewpoints.
This will not work.
what we say and do what we do through our viewpoints
Through our viewpoints all becomes clear. It will soon be illogical
It will seem illogical, but at least you will understand
Says this is the key to a successful implementation of no context
You must understand your foe before you can ever hope to defeat him. You need to work out
why we act as we do, why we will take certain steps in so understanding you maximize your prospects of executing and, most importantly, maintaining no context.
Okay.
Okay, the professionals of the therapist are well aware of how effective the concept of
no contact is.
They will have a rudimentary understanding as to why it is effective, but they cannot
tell you with any precision or detail just why it is effective in the way that the narcissist
can.
It is in the way that I can.
There are plenty of victims or survivors, if they use that word instead, who have lived
through the entanglement with the narcissist.
The victim has experienced a dizzying seduction, the mesmerizing golden period where they are
get to meet their soulmates. They were bombarded with love and affection and placed on the pedestal.
They then experienced the incomprehensible and vicious devaluation as they found themselves
hated and despised by the narcissist even though they had no understanding of why this was happening
to them. They clung on desperately trying to establish why were they being treated in such
an awful fashion. They hung on trying to return to the golden period before they were cast aside
As they sat days to confuse, the narcissist hoovered them up again and easily pulled them
back into the false reality. The victim went willingly since he or she had no comprehension
that this was but a further step along the road when one couples with the narcissist.
The victim will have been pushed and pulled over many years and will have many battle stories
about the war they fought with the narcissist. Certainly the recollections from a victim have
the discard and the Hoover. They know the moves and can identify the red flags once they have been
able to recover and view the whole torrid affair from a reasonable distance of objectivity.
All this puts them in a strong position to provide others with advice and there is admittedly
considerable value in their recollections. However, they may still not understand why
certain things happened. They will not have grasped why the narcissist behaved in certain
what to look for, but the victim clearly does not know.
The narcissist is inside out, okay?
Okay, so is that interesting?
So yeah, prepare for the crusades,
why wouldn't you want to do that?
He says, this is a fact that, let me see.
The more contact occurs, the greater the ignition of the mixture of the subsequent severe difficulties and resisting its effects, right?
Unfortunately for you, you'll never be able to completely eradicate yourself from you because of this existence of the mixture
I've achieved this absolutely on purpose. I will have shattered your being in your heart and you will repair most of it
You will eventually conquer the shame of being hoodwings. You'll restore your finances in the broken home
You will reduce and extinguish the anxiety and trauma you felt it will take a long time
It will take effort and discipline, but she will get there
You will, however, not be able to repair your heart entirely.
There will always be a small crack, a hairline fracture, and a slight puncture hole in it.
This is the permanent effect of having dance with me.
I know that crack is there, and if ever given the chance, I will activate the mixture as
it creeps through the crack, seeps through the fracture, and trickles into the hole.
From there, it will start to grow and multiply as the mixture rages.
through you. It seeks to open you up making everything seem wonderful once more and remind
you all the brilliant things that we did together during our golden period. This will then haul
you back into the nightmare with me once again. Ah, I think Bita's okay. I talked to her, you know,
It is a fact that you will always carry this vulnerability, it is part of our design, it
is the necessary consequence of how we affect you.
This means that you are always at risk of being influenced from us again and that is
why you must remain your vigilance and no contact forever.
Do not think after 10 years that you can contact me and be safe from the MMI influence.
You are always in danger, there is no hope other than to remain away from me because
I hope she's okay.
Okay.
But it is the most effective tool in dealing with, you know, it's like, if you're being psychologically messed with, it's just to remove yourself from the situation.
So it says, according to the, here's the, when you implement the no contact, the following occurs. It says, implementation of the low, no contact.
It says, they lost their primary source of fuel. Okay.
So it's as initial grand Hoover seeking to recover primary source
There's gonna be a big no big, you know love bombing Hoover says of the Hoover successful no contacts defeated
Primary source reinstated with bonus of Hoover fuel
Whoever fails, no contacts maintained, chaos period ensues.
So frenzied attempts by us to identify and implement new primary sources while draining
and losing supplementary sources.
Then stabilization, new primary sources established, depleted and lost supplementary sources are
now replaced.
Stabilization, how new period primary source established, depleted, and lost supplementary
resources are replaced.
Opportunities sought to affect you, who were against you, and defeat no contact.
By knowing these stages will occur, and also by understanding what's involved in each
of these, you'll be prepared to deal with them and maintain no contact.
Okay.
But it is hard to execute, right?
because of empathy or empathic traits.
It is of course your empathic nature and traits which cause you to be chosen by us in the first place.
The fact that you have our caring, honest, and decent individual means that you become a target to someone like me.
We know that by exhibiting such empathic traits that you are ideal for our purposes.
Because one, you are a devotee of the concept of love.
Two, you will readily be swept off your feet by the outpouring of our supposed love for you.
Three, you'll respond to our love bombing in a positive way.
Four, you will provide fuel in response to our seduction.
Five, you will not depart once our devaluation commences,
but instead you will remain trying to fix us and heal us.
You will want to make things right.
Six, you will provide fuel during our devaluation of you.
And seven, you will be susceptible
to our attempts to hoover you.
Thanks.
Okay.
So, I mean, this is a good lot of good information because it is something you're gonna, it's not just something you can easily do, right?
It's what, it'll be difficult for no context, especially when you're in that traumatized state, right?
So, I don't know if you've been through this. That's too much. That's too much. Oh, I'm sorry.
Yeah, it is too much, I mean it is too much, but it's like it's important to know, you know
Power plays
So we'll go into the things like so once you do the so all of a sudden the other
Emergency they'll see if you respond to the emergency and you know people we will probably
Always be there to respond to these emergencies, right?
Well, you know, if you're empathic, right, then they don't work in threats and then they don't work. It is like then
You do other things
You pretend to on a lag or something people do a lot of things and they have sex to you and they have all these kind of things, okay?
Incoming it's a white night, right?
false criminal allegations.
There's a lot of power plays they use, right?
What's this one?
It says, oh.
Give like 20 of them. This is a lot of good information in here guys. I'll let you read this book. It's by H.G. Tudor
Okay, that I read through the whole book right if that was this book was called no contact how to beat the
Narcissist but then I respond to the whole book. Yes, he's by H.G. Tudor
He's really interesting.
He's actually a narcissist,
and so he writes from the point of view as a narcissist,
but he gives good information about how they can act, right?
And then I was reading the devil's toolkit,
like I was reading about yesterday,
It starts with the thought of interruption, right?
Then they institute the chisel of misery.
So this is our very handy instrument that we have in our...
In our toolkit, we use it on a frequent basis to chip away at yourself esteem
It is a necessary consequence of our need that for fuel that we must identify those appliances
That will supply it to us in a satisfactory quantity and of excellent quality
We harvest our fuel from many sources throughout our daily lives
But we always like to have one prime appliance which gives us the majority of our supply the powers
This provides us with reassurance that there will be fuel available and it lessens the need to extract it from too many sources, which in turn uses a considerable amount of our energy.
This means that our prime source of supply is invariably someone who's empathic individual.
We are highly skilled at detecting empaths and once we have identified that someone has these empathic traits, we latch on to them and will not let go until we decide what we should do so.
The ultimate empathy.
is the codependent, and we've reveled in securing a supply line from someone who fits that description.
It is an unfortunate...
A consequence, however, that when we secure supply from an empath, they are imbued with
a high degree of self-esteem.
At first, this does not send a problem.
As a positive fuel, you provide us during the golden period of our interaction is of
very good quality.
Your caring and compassionate nature causes you to be effusive in your praise and admiration,
your love and attentiveness towards us.
become derelict in your duties and the taste of your positive fuel becomes too familiar.
This combination of you lessening your attention and the contempt that comes from familiarity
means that we must shift the emphasis of our harvesting of fuel. We must move from the positive
to the negative for in doing we we reach the walls of a new and vast reservoir of fuel.
that we are able to avail ourselves of the reservoir of negative fuel means we must overcome
that self-esteem that you are imbued with. As an empath, you will have high sense of self-worth
arising from the nature of your character. You perform acts of compassion, you care for others,
and you
derive great satisfaction from doing so. Your self-esteem is not born from arrogance or
smugness, but rather from the knowledge that you have helped someone. You placed on your arm around
someone and understood his or her pain and concerns. We know because we watched you do this often enough.
The self-esteem means that initially you may prove resistant to our attempts to extract the
negative fuel from you. This means we must reach into our toolkit and wrap our fingers around the
This is an instrument of subtlety, whereas the saw of interruption is regressive and brash, the chisel of misery, by contrast, is used in a manner which means you might not even realize it's being wielded against you.
There are some chisels which are heavy with a dull head, the purpose of these chisels is to wedge and break, as if one is trying to crack a brick into.
The chisel of misery is not fashioned in that way, it has been designed so that it gradually caves and shifts away to reduce your sense of self worth.
Little by little, over a long period, the head of the chisel is very fine, ultra-sharp,
and is able to carve away the slightest piece of your self-esteem so that you will not even
notice.
Over time, in a steady application of the chisel of misery, it will remove more and
more of your self-esteem so that when you suddenly realize how much it has been eroded,
it is too late.
The chisel has a mushroom head, which is intentionally designed because the nature of the instrument is just like a mushroom to keep you in the dark and pile shit on top of you.
The chisel will be used during our devaluation of you on a daily basis.
It applies so that we are able to exert our influence over you in order to take control of the way you act and you are unable to resist.
Let's take them, sterilize you through being mesmerized and amazed.
The chisel is not an overt tool of manipulation.
It's effective in this arises from its continued application
each and every day, like water dripping on a forehead.
Bit by bit, we chip away at what makes you, you,
reducing your capacity for critical thinking,
lowering your resistance, and ensuring
that we are opening you up for that application
of other tools and manipulations in due course.
The chisel has an insidious march
and is very difficult for you to detect.
Its light touch almost feels like a pleasant caress, and indeed the misery that comes from
the application of this tool usually comes bound up in some form of flattery that is
designed to deceive.
Examples of this include the following comments.
I love you, but I wish you would not go out so often.
I like you to have friends, but Sandra is not a good person to spend time with.
I have only your best interest at heart.
That dress wouldn't be appropriate at any other time, but not when you are going out
I know you work hard, but you really should be dedicating more time to us.
The children would benefit if you stayed at home rather than worked, you know?
The comments are all representative of the chisel marks we make.
They come dressed as compliments that are really designed to put you down in the city
accumulation of such comments over time will have the effect of wearing you down the same
A master craftsman, such as I, must use the chisel of misery.
In the hands of a clumsy man, it might be driven too deep, and it turns the gouges into
a chunk from you.
This runs the risk of alerting you to the use, and therefore only a skilled practitioner
can be trusted to delicately apply the chisel and lift away feathers' weight of self-esteem,
slowly accurately.
With each pressing application of the chisel, layer upon layer of self-worth is stripped
away.
The crafting is exquisite and impressive.
You have no idea what is being done to you with this device until eventually you find
yourself demeaned, exhausted, and low in self-esteem.
How did that happen?
How did you come to this innest position?
Your confusion increases as you try to establish what has actually happened to you.
You cannot point to one specific act or event that brought you so low.
it is the chisel of misery that has been applied against you and has achieved a stated purpose once
again. When your self-worth is shaved away in the fashion, then you are weakened. You are unable
to think clearly. You do not trust your instincts. This means that you will cling more tightly to us
as we offer you a way forward. You will believe more and more what we say, especially with the
gas torch being applied, but more on that later, and come to trust in what we say as
and do as being right for you.
We have whittled away your defenses and left you exposed.
The chisel has done its job in stripping you of any capacity
by which you can resist us and now enables us
to apply other methods of manipulation and control upon you.
The chisel is an insidious in its application, but its eventual effect is of a devastating
nature.
Our steady methodical and practice application of this instrument will invariably bring about
the desired results and you will always be left wondering how on earth we did it.
Wunder no longer, you have met the chisel of misery.
Then we have the hammer of intimidation. I'm gonna go to the gas gas thing
pliers and manipulation, let me see the gas torch roast and spectacles
unlimited tape
The
There's a lot in this toolbox a lot installation tape
Portion of illumination.
I do not know how this found its way into my toolkit.
I certainly did not put it there, and I did not ask for anyone else to put it inside my
toolkit.
I recall that I once was groping about for a suitable instrument.
When I came upon this instead, I recognized it as a torch, but as I slid the button backwards
and straightforward, nothing happened.
I sat there in the dark, moving the button forward and weighty, but there was no response.
I slid it back into place and gave the torch a shake, as if trying to wake it up from its
I then moved the button forward again but the torch remained inactive.
I moved the button back and forth vigorously as if doing so would somehow jolt it into life
but there was still no response. I toyed with throwing it this to one side discarding it
as I would do with one of my victims but I decided against taking the step.
There must be some reason for its inclusion in my toolbox although I wasn't able to fathom
what it was. There was a bulb in place and the casing was not broken yet. It still, it would not work.
I wondered whether this had been surreptitiously secreted into my toolbox by one of my empathic
victims.
Perhaps they had been planning an escape from my clutches, and this formed part of their
departure plan.
I placed the torch down and just rummaged inside the toolbox to see if there was a rope,
a ladder, a shovel, or some wire cutters.
I did not find any of these items, and therefore concluded that either the empath was woefully
Alternatively, the empath has not actually put this torch in there as in the first place
in order to escape.
I was puzzled.
I will readily admit this, and I do not like the state of such affairs.
I must always know what is going on you see.
This accords with my omnipotence and my omniscient state.
You must understand that when you are special and as gifted as someone like me, it comes
This is required because otherwise, those who seek to unseat me, sadly there are a handful
of such diluted fools who wish to bring this about, would be able to plot against me without
me knowing about them doing so. I have to have full awareness of what is going on around me so
that I can quash this traitorous behavior promptly and brutally. No uprising is ever
dealt with peacefully. Force must always be applied if you are to eradicate any such dissents.
This necessity of knowing resulted in me needing to ascertain why this particular piece of
kit has found its way into my toolkit.
I am a bright man.
I possess substantial intelligence and common with many, although not all of our kinds.
You have to be clever to plot and scheme like we do in order to bring about the harvesting of fuel.
Accordingly, I applied my sizable mind to the task of working out why there was a torch inside my toolkit.
It was not mine. I knew that it was not part or was unlikely to be part of any escape package and therefore had to have some other purpose.
I could not carry for long with this puzzle because there was fuel for me to gather.
But the day had been so productive, so far, I had time to apply this to this task.
After due consideration, I realized what purpose this instrument served.
It had not been placed there by an empath, it had not been placed there for one of my
empathic victims.
It had been placed there for one of my empathic victims.
Some intruder had casually added this torch into my toolkit to enable whoever my victim
was to shed some light on their situation.
Yes, that was it.
The intention was to allow the particular person to see what was really going.
It was to penetrate my murky, shadowy world and spread light around.
It was the torch of illumination.
Some interfering individual was seeking to supplant me by leading this tool for use by someone else.
I could not have that.
Any clarification from the bright light of enlightenment was entirely a bad thing,
which would usurp my control and threaten my supremacy.
There was no way I could allow any of my victims to use the tool against me.
This would be beyond the pale.
I had lifted the torch, having now established in the fairest purpose, ready to bring it
down on the cold hard ground and smash it into a hundred pieces, but I stopped.
I had no need to break this tool, for it was not working anyway.
I had checked the torch and tried it many times, and it was not fit for its purpose.
I would actually gain far more satisfaction in preserving it rather than destroying it.
Should a victim reach into my toolbox and bind this torch, their hopes re-lifted as
they would think that they had found something to light the way ahead.
They would believe they had something that would leave them out of the darkness and
away from my influence.
Yet, such a relation would turn to despair when they attempted to use the device.
Yes, that would be entirely satisfying.
Their shaking hands would grasp the torch.
and as their fingers fumbled through the switch I would watch in great anticipation
as the button would slide back and forth and nothing would happen how delicious their misery
would be when they realized that the torch of illumination would not work it then dawned on
me that the reason why this torch did not work I twisted the end of the torch and it came away
revealing the space inside where the batteries would be placed there were no batteries inside
Please that I worked out what this device was for and satisfied that it could actually be used to my advantage
I placed the end back on twisted it in place and replaced it amidst the other tools and readiness for a helpless victim to come upon it
Yeah, what's up
Hey, what's up? Oh, I'm one second. I don't know. I'm like a little bit. There we go. Okay. Hello
Hello
Not bad. How are you doing? Good morning?
Chilling chilling. Oh, yeah, all that reading was kind of like losing people interest. I wanted to you know
Pop up for a minute. So let me ask you a question. How was your you said you had a dinner earlier, right with your family? Uh-huh
How'd that go? How was it? It was good. This type of some enchiladas and
Didn't help her a little bit and had a beer
Hang out with the family a little bit so yeah, yeah, nah, I stopped by I stopped by earlier
I seen like you were supposed to go live and then I think it was like nine o'clock or something like that
Yeah, yeah
Stopped in at 10. I stopped that. I was like, oh what the fuck is going on? I'm sorry. Yeah, I'm okay. I'm just saying
Yeah, it's nice to meet you Luigi
Yeah, it's a rogue nomad. It's a yeah rogue. It's a state's hurt and rogue nomad. We'll meet each other
You're a rogue. What's up, bro? Hey, great. There you go. There you go
I'll be the mucky in the middle. So yeah, so I was everything. Oh, yeah
Ro you're from the states. He asked oh
I'm sorry. I didn't hear you. Yes, sir from the western United States
Alright, cool, cool. How about you? Yeah, yeah east coast
I think that is no, I'm not talking I'm thinking that a lot of panelists and a lot of people in the chat are actually victims of
Narcissist and so and I've actually experienced in real life the cycles and everything
Yeah, which one did the one with the there's one I was reading just now is called the devil's tool kit
And then the one before that was called no contact and the one before that was called how to control co-dependent people or something like that
and they're kind of
The first one was written as a statire,
but the other ones were written by an actual narcissist
who actually writes these books and shares his techniques
and his worldview.
It was very interesting reading,
but I think part of the whole social experience
is discussing it afterwards.
So I think like Louis and I had the same idea
of just contributing.
Okay, perfect, that's what...
Well, my thoughts on the
on on that I
Yeah, it's very insightful very interesting, but at the same time it's like
To what extent does that just ruin the chance of any relationship between a man and a woman?
Because for example, like if I have a girlfriend, I don't want her to wear this sexy as outfit to the gym
so
Like that doesn't make me a narcissist or blah blah just makes me like a normal human male
They I don't think any dude is gonna want to his girlfriend to wear. Yeah, that just makes you a man
That just makes you a regular man. Exactly
There's plenty of men that like to have their girlfriend look like you know look how she wants to look it looks sexy
That's right. Sorry, but let me tell you something like like if I'm if I'm with my bitch, right?
I'd say like this if I'm with my girl
She could look as sexy as she wants dresses slutty as she wants. However you want to put it however you want to quote
Long as she's with me
Yeah, and we're somewhere at least I'm in control of the situation
But like if she goes somewhere with let's just say her girlfriends or she goes to the gym like like somebody said earlier
You know, that's a little different. I'm not in control of that situation. I listen. I could trust her
But I can't trust like I can't trust other dudes trying to come up to you you get I'm saying
So why put your like I'm looking at like if you're my girl why why are you dressing like that?
Like I would question that you know, I don't have that issue, but I'm just saying like
Sure, I mean, but I think that's like a dad's real thing
Where it's like you but the thing would be like the guy would be like wondering what she's dressing like
I like that for other people the other people the tension or she's dressing like that for me or for herself
You always act and they always I know I'm gonna cut you off my best side
But like women will always tell you oh, I'm doing it for me if they get a boob job
But oh, I just did it for me like like make myself feel better. No, bitch
You wanted other dudes to sit there and look at you stop playing like don't lie
Like you want other dudes to acknowledge the way you look
There's confidence in this equation where the woman is the narcissist and she's kind of like deceiving the man to just accept it
To be like well, I better fucking handle it mother fucker
Yeah, there's different times. Well, let's call this like a I guess that's called like a somatic narcissist
Which is like a narcissist that's really into the body and like they're usually very attractive people
But they usually get you know a lot of surgery or like a lot of working out and it can be extreme in there
Yeah, so yeah, but then they can deal with it another kind of narcissist
We are so we have the people you have narcissists together and you know, they kind of like
But I'm not so you this right at the same time. I'll tell you like I don't
don't see a problem with a woman wanting to fix her body no matter what the
reason is even if it's like it is for men you know what I mean like just to
get acknowledged and look that and it like if that's what makes them feel
good like I can't knock it
Yeah, I can't I'm not knocking it. Oh
I mean, it's it's actually a motivator you can look you can work out at home, right?
But why would you do that when you can go and be around this gorgeous girls?
That they just work on their bodies and they put attention to their outfits
They're a big motivator for me to make it to the fucking gym. I'm not gonna lie
I feel what you're saying. I look at it like on a whole another level like I work out, right?
personally um i work out with my son and we get it in but like we we we go with no girls is that
we're not going there for the girls do we want to look good for the girl for women absolutely but
do we want to stay healthy like the re the real reason i work out is to to be healthy you know
I said on the cake or however you want to put it you get what I'm saying
When I go when I go to work out there's no women there
I think when you said at a whole other level it's something that I cannot understand because
I'm not a parent and if I were working out like with my child I everything will radically
change so absolutely you are approaching fitness at a whole different level that I do not understand.
Oh nah but I'm saying look even if I was just like just to work out by myself dolo like
I would not go where women are.
Because that's not the main motive it like I don't want to go to a gym just to see women
No, I'm going to the gym to work out
I'm going to the gym to work out look good and they get women
But you would find it was you would find it distracting because you might be like looking at the bus
Yeah, like that's not yeah, I don't want to like I'm not trying to see that. I'm trying to be masculine
Energetic testosterone boosting it. You know me like
I don't want to sit there and look at I'm saying like that's just not the scene for the women at that moment
You know
That's all I'm saying like I'm not going to the gym to look. I don't want to go gym and see women like
I operate on a lower level because I do enjoy looking at the women work like the outfits and make it's motivating to me because
I'm talking about this. That's right. It's like
I think it creates a standard for the woman that I want, you know, I mean, like if I'm
putting all this effort into my own body, like it creates a standard to the woman that
I want to be with, but I'm a single man.
So, at the same time, if I were in a committed relationship, let alone being a parent, I have
no idea how approached it is, so I'm operating on many levels below you, and I don't understand,
you know, approaching it from such a level of responsibility that you are, and I respect
that immensely.
I look up to it, I think it's-
I'm not right and you're wrong or vice versa like it. No, it sounds like it's legit. How can I ask how old you are? I
Am older than I sound which is not good. I'm 38
So we're then at the same age. Okay. All right
Yeah, just like I
at this point I don't
I've dedicated my whole life to career. I'm extremely happy what I'm at with my career and
I still do, this may sound very selfish
and I'm open to criticism over it,
but I will never want a woman to tell me
how to conduct my career just to be a good parent
or a good husband, hence why I'm single.
I still want to conduct my career
and I'm very happy with it
and I'm not willing to change that,
perhaps down the road.
if I'm not fucking dead, but it's just, you know, and I, I, I part of my career,
like I find immense motivation in, in people who are parents and serving them and making sure that they
have a beautiful life with their children. Um, but I, I'm very dedicated to my duty, my career.
Yeah, well, I think it comes down to like me, but maybe like, you know, so people that know people that kind of like worry about like
If they would stray or if they're looking at other people
They're maybe they're like more apt to like worry about other people like their own their own spouse like cheating too
But I think like if there's some couples that can trust each other hundred percent and the husband knows like she can be out with
Gay friends you can go out with even like a
Having male person she knows and not
be at a risk of cheating because the relationship will be so strong, there will not be a doubt.
There's a lot of doubt when it comes to the people that are mad about cheating. There's
always this suspicion that people are cheating in those situations, but it might be. There could
be a reason to be suspicious for some people and there could be a reason not to be suspicious for
some people, so I guess it just depends on the particular unique situation.
Yeah, absolutely, absolutely very subjective and
If is that not the most complicated thing that a human can
Accomplish is actually like
Love is that not the most complicated thing?
You know, you can find a career you can be successful. You can buy a house
vehicle
Everything but as far as nailing
romance and
love
It's something that can fuck you up so bad as you've read the whole night
So it's and nobody there's no blueprint as far as how to succeed at it
So it's as like and it's like also I want to stay I'm sorry don't interrupt it
It's like where it's not like everybody you get your data is not going to be an art. They are relatively
Rare like a rare to find I mean they're more common now and maybe a certain communities
They're gonna be more common, but it's they it is kind of usually rare and but it's like you will meet them
They'll kind of fuck up your whole
World view of everything and so it's like they're very good at that and so I just you know you meet one and then you know
That will just know that can do it. It's not good, but it's not gonna be everybody
Look, it will keep you from trusting other people though
It will make it hard for trust and going to a new relationship and I'll make it harder even to like trust friends and stuff like that. It can be very
Yeah, it can make it cynical. We can make it quite cynical. Oh, yeah
But I think it there's a lot of strength and
And getting your heart broken and continuing to love. I think there's a lot of strength in there
I'm sure that even we don't without being parents or married or anything some people lose a pet
They lose a dog and they'll be like I'm never getting another dog for the rest of my life
They're just afraid to experience the heartbreak again
So I think there's a lot of courage and bravery in putting ourselves through the
You know to the potential pain once again a roll a roll would it be fair to say like would it be fair for me to say you've been
You've been in a long relationship and like things got you know kind of fucked up between you and her
You know not I
Perhaps it sounds that way, but even though I'm 38 the longest relationship has been in has been three years
I've just not been a big relationship guy
Yeah, don't knock I mean don't knock three years because three years is still
You know a decent amount of time
Don't sell yourself short man
Appreciate it, but that's still a minute like a lot of emotions and this and that
Could take place within the first six months. Yeah, so three years. You know, that's that's a decent amount of time
Yeah, well, I can definitely say that that one was one that taught me a lot and
Give me and from then on I've been hyper aware hyper vigilant per se
Okay, yeah, yeah, it's just before so you to avoid going in that kind of relationship again or
Yeah
That's what and sometimes we will be but we'll be attracted to certain people and that will find it and we'll be attracted for there's some lessons usually
They get sometimes it's like but we there's some people will be attracted to we don't know and we'll go in the same
Be attracted to certain types of people that will
either be femme fatale, or there'll be our own, you know,
onomatopoejections and sometimes the dangerous one.
And so, you know, we should really have to remember to like,
you know, be in a great relationship with yourself
before you, you know, delve into other people
because it will very much be much more complicated.
You're dealing with another person
in a way you don't have control over
and a lot of people like, they need that control.
And so, until you can learn to compromise,
that control is probably best not to...
You're in a relationship, right? Yeah, anyway
Yeah, you can tell you you're ready, you know, you have to be ready
No, or else we'll just keep attracting you wrong relationships in our life, right?
Well, you know, I think those are friendships come along like if you have good friends you have to watch each other's backs you
You have the authority within the friendship to say perhaps I don't think this person is the best for you
As tough as it may be for that person to take it, but I think you know loving yourself having a strong circle
It's something extremely important before you try to love anybody else. That's right
And they also like, you know, the amount of people you can probably trust as friends, you know
It would be true friends. I'll be there for you and I just
Disturbed love you or you know, if you have enough you can count on one hand
It's gonna be yourself a blessed person because a lot of people don't have one person, you know
Absolutely, and I think that you you
You present a vehicle for many of us to you know develop easy explain that easy easy explain that
What what the fuck do you what do you think you even know about me?
Explain what you just said what the fuck do you think you know about me taking relationship advice from state term?
What the fuck do you think you know about me family?
Come up top and talk you shit
Um rogue my bad guy. I had as much as playing real quick. Good. Good
Yeah
How are you doing no man doing good
Did yes, I finished a huge project at work that I had been working on for the past month
It was a complete success, client was super happy through it, I was able to buy a whole
new vehicle, buy a new weapon, afforded surgery, I had a tumor that had to get removed.
So it was a huge success, I'm very, very happy and now I'm just like, what now?
Which is, you know, it's a good thing, it's a great thing.
You get so cut up in the project and the work that it feels almost like wow, like I have all this time, right?
Like that's why in part why I'm allowed to be here Tuesday mornings. I will be
Usually having to start like 3 a.m. Like I will wake up at 3 a.m. And listen to your show as it's going on and the craziness
but
It's I'm free now, which is this excellent. I'm doing very well. Thank you very much for asking. How are you taking?
Good. How are you?
I'm just you hear me. Hold on. Yeah
Hello, sorry
Okay, so I'm sorry about that. Do you hear me? Okay?
Yeah
Okay, good. Yeah, so yeah, so we you know, and we're all
Consider ourselves lucky, you know, we have people that love us and we have a
Yeah roof over our head and you know foodie we were very lucky so
Most of us are seeing this country for not the answer. Absolutely. We're much better off than people in a lot of places
And so and a lot more opportunities and a lot more right a lot more hope for for us
Then a lot of people feel so, you know, don't lose that hope
Yep
So what's up with that hot mess summer I wish that she would join the panel
Yeah, I mean she was I mean, you know you heard the song earlier tonight
I'll try I'm trying to make a road. No, man. I like how she's like she's so
feisty. I like women like that like that. They're so
She was in the chat earlier she might she might still be here I
Tempted to go to long very well with women like that
Just
Do you know or not?
No, I don't know.
It's just like that type of personality.
Not even like in a romantic kind of sense, but just like...
Like being a chef.
At work and stuff.
I've dealt with a lot of women like that and we have...
We've always become good friends.
Are you aware that Summer has a channel too or not?
Yeah, I'm subscribed.
Okay, okay
Yes, indeed summer has two channels on two channels actually I was like at her show
Whenever shows talk your age last night, and she also has hot mess summer the mod can
Put that in the chat that'd be great
Let's see and
Yeah, it was for summer too summer is awesome
There you go
Like that back
I got the colors very nice
Yeah, we have like it subscribe. I got the songs going I got the I've been doing a lot of stuff on canva guys
I have also the emojis. I put like the 10 emojis. I can
For more
But if you forgot hit the like button real quick to you two seconds just swipe down from the chair hit the like come right back
Yeah, thank you. Yeah, I got a new like it subscribe
graphics up to two. Uh yeah there's a lot of cool stuff you can do with the streamer graphics. I'm just
realizing like uh especially you know now that I'm seeing some examples and stuff like there's a lot of
cool stuff you can do to you know. Have you watched the latest season of Squid Game? Uh I've never
Episodes where they just run down the whole season like yeah, I'm just I know the plot of it
I just don't I don't watch the show, you know, I don't really watch TV. Do you like it?
Yes, I love it. It did last season was it dark is when it was really really really dark
I was not expecting that and they kind of hint that
They're gonna continue, but it's gonna be in the United States
Which is cool. I was I was just thinking like I don't know if where you live in LA
They have like the Korean fried chicken and like Korean corn dogs like I've noticed that there's some
Stuff that South Korea has been able to successfully export to the United States, which is like amazing
Mm-hmm and quitting entertainment like that shows quit me
Yeah
Yeah, but sometimes it's like you know
The arts there is a difference in TV show and reality, but yeah, sometimes they you know the reality of TV shows will
And movies will imitate reality, but a lot of times the reality imitates them, right?
so
Be careful with the entertainment we consume and what what they're trying to do
You know a psyche easy wants you to pin the link
Okay, he wants to come up here come on
I got you baby girl you hurt. I got you
I
Fucking spoil everything
See me young Slayer, mr. Easy, I'm sorry don't apologize for nothing who the fuck I see
Mr. Easy, sorry fuck easy who the fuck is easy
Easy yeah, who's easy
Easy cameras on he's in the chat. He's you know easy
Shit, but he means like who the fuck is easy like how I'm talking who the fuck ain't no fucking body
We're all we're all human beings. We are all human beings. Yes, sir. We are we are some of us a little less than others
Yeah, but I mean that's the thing about all men being created equal, you know, it's kind of like just seeing equal under the law
Absolutely, you know, you got good citizens you got scumbags you got uh, you know, you got um
regular
Average Joe's and you got pieces of shit. I mean the list goes on, you know
And would that be fair to say like I mean, I'm just saying somebody that um
Commits crimes compared to an average citizen
You think like both of them share the same
Equal um status in life
Well, it's like, you know
Crimes yes, well, it depends on the type of crime I suppose it's like, you know, there's people that are you know
Are going after other people it's the human beings. It's like, you know, pray
You know what how about this? We don't even have to take it that far. How about how about we put it like this
How about if I just came on your stream every day, right?
And just bashed you like you know like on some shit like I don't like you and I'm just
Throwing slurs at you and fucking with you and talking shit to you every single fucking day of your life
Eventually what what's gonna happen?
You would what you would block me, right?
Yeah
Yeah, that's my point like, you know, you have you have regular human beings that can have a conversation
They kick it and this and that and everything will be smooth the whole night. You get this one
Person and I'm not even targeting a specific person. I'm just saying anybody you get one dickhead out of the group that could fuck
Everything up nine people could be up here having a whole conversation
Yeah, have a respect for one another
You know stop I talk you talk blah blah blah back and forth and you get that one dickhead
They just wants to run his mouth all night run his mouth all night pop shit took this that you know
You get what I'm saying. Yeah
That goes back to the criminal and the average Joe type of thing
They get treated equally. No, they don't
And they're having one stays home
Yeah, but there's also there's also there's also psychopaths and like there's psychopaths that are like, you know
CEOs and are you know, you know, very high in the in the world or there's one psychopaths that are
You know low level low level criminals and stuff like that. So it's like you can use your you can use these traits
For positive or negative as far as he's like
Including psychopaths. He's talking like an asshole
like i'm talking i'm talking like what i'm talking about for people in prisons like a lot of people
in prisons are considered are like on the you know spectrum of of antisocial because you know
that it's crime itself is antisocial right and so it's the thing we we trace back it comes down
to the question of nature against nurture which i think both factors apply like sometimes
If you have like the same kid that could become a world-class athlete,
put in the wrong environment, will channel that drive into crime.
So I think that nature and nurture both play a big role as far as
Like if you're gonna become a huge asshole, or you're gonna serve others
But I also one thing that we all as humans need to take into consideration is
trauma and
Our response to it like with trauma you can either become a continuation of it
And just kind of like become a worse manifestation of how you got traumatized or
You can channel
What happened to you to prevent others from experiencing the trauma?
So I think our response to trauma is quite dependent on if you become a piece of shit
Become somebody who protects others from that piece of shit
But actually you're gonna be a piece of shit or you're gonna be an
Upstanding decent human being you don't got to be perfect, but you could be decent you could be decent
You could be a piece of shit
Right. Well, it's like yeah, because you know, we know we know this saying hurt people hurt people but also, you know
There's people like like there's the cycles of you know
There's the wounded healer and I say there's people that are cycle breakers and their generational cycle breakers because a lot of these behaviors will carry on from previous
Generations of our family and they're really passed down for maybe hundreds of years or thousands of years, maybe you know, and
Maybe we're the first person
All right, so let me ask you a question. I bombed so
If somebody like you said before hurt people hurt people. That's a fact. So let's just say for instance, I'm gonna give you an example
What if what if right a
Heart person hurt somebody right did his time for it, right?
He did his time for it came back and was like a a good citizen
opposed to
Somebody that was in the same situation or her person and her people
That that that you know, maybe got punished for a little something or whatever and went back to doing what he was doing
Now do you see two different?
Do you see two different examples in both of those people?
Well, yeah, because there's you know, there's people that will be rehabilitated in prison
Maybe they'll find right fine religion or they'll they'll get a career after they'll like use the time to get a skill
They'll you know, and you know, so or there'll be people that are just you know, they're just waiting to
Just not be a piece of shit anymore, right? Yeah
Right, okay. There's one factor that that I
I've learned, placed a pretty big role in this, which is IQ, intelligence, because if
somebody doesn't have a proper IQ to understand that...
Their actions are leading to all of this
demise of their own life and the life of others if they cannot comprehend that they're a lot more prone to
Continuing I think that the the more intelligent you are they hire which is genetic
Back to just nature. I think the higher chances that you have to be able to
Perhaps have the self-awareness to break the cycle of
Whatever the fuck brought you to that point, which you know, there's no judgment of what your ancestors did to bring you there
But the higher the IQ the more the higher chances to break that cycle in my opinion
This is not in anything professional at all. Just
Right, it's just depends on but it depends on how the people will like you know how it's maybe how different things about you know
You know like if you unalive somebody here
You know you're unalive somebody and then you serve a 50 years in prison, right?
You come out like you're still gonna be charged or so we judge for unaliving somebody if people know the story
You know even they fear if you're totally know that even like Charles Manson's
The woman that
Yeah, I killed the Charles Manson. She's got released from prison, but she'll still always be
Judged as like the person that did that. I mean, you know, but you know, you can't change and it's like, you know
People people are always gonna assume you think what they're gonna want to think
You know the thing without people is that people are gonna think what they want to think and so you have to let them
You just don't want people, you know, we have some dangerous things with like kind of like which hunts and like, you know, like little
People like to get in a little like we're doing the purge. We're doing this we're sending this group away this group away this group away
And it's like, you know, it's like well what they go for one group though
They'll go for another group and they go to go for the next group. It's like what you know who's ultimately, you know
So I think that and also some people don't make some people also they'll
Rehabilitate but they'll never get the forgiveness and so they're like what what's the point of like
Rehabilitating if I'll never get to forgiveness about if I never there's no chance of redemption at all
We'll always be looking the same way. I never looked at like I can change
It's been why what's the what's the incentive to change really? Oh, hi, right?
Hello, you know me. How you doing?
That was it
No finding me. Yeah, I know if I thought you were having a nice
Yeah, now you can talk right at the same time with that situation, right?
Like, you know, you're talking about somebody that on a live somebody but no no to know like no two
situations are the same because
Somebody could do it with the intent and then somebody can do it
Defending themselves like if somebody broke into your house
For instance, and then you have been to on a live that person
Right. So you shouldn't be in the wrong like like like and even as far as morality and and and religion
Even if you want to take it that far like it should be justified because you was just protecting yourself
At that particular moment of time
Yeah, that's good that you're looking at you're looking at you're looking at specific you're really saying you're saying okay
So look at the specific
I'm just playing devil's advocate and saying both sides like okay you can do it with the intent or you can do it defending yourself and in like no two situations are exactly the same you know
19 or something like they had a girlfriend and then she was 17 and he was 19 or something like that
right it was just like and then so he has put on a sex offender registry because he was it's
statutory that the parents charge or something to 17 the parents get mad at him they charge okay so
what so was that is that person versus like he's not he's going to be looked at as some like even
that are people going to look at the situation or is it just the fact that he's on the on the registry
And that's another situation, but if I'm not mistaken, right?
I believe there is a two-year thing like for instance like if
like if a
male or female whatever doesn't matter is 19 and the other significant person is
17 I think that's okay
of you know lawfully lawfully I you know and I'm not right I'm a lawyer I'm just saying what I thought I heard before I might have read
That's all I'm saying. Um, yeah, I think if it's more than two years
Then I think it's like a problem like if it's 1916 or you know like 18 or 15 or something like that
Then that's what I think is
It's a problem here. It's 21 21 and 70 it's 21 and 17
That's that's like probably the five years next topic. No, but it's an interesting topic to talk about because I actually know
somebody that would like when I was on on a registry because of that the same thing
I think he was like 21
You know, I just heard the story. I just know about this and he's having problems because you know
It's like that will follow you when you're convicted of that kind of thing, right?
Yeah, to me like if you're both teenagers, you know what I mean? It's not that crazy like it
Not if you're like 19 and then then she's 13. No, that's crazy
Yeah, I'm talking about the high teens. Okay
Nineteen six nineteen and seventeen like that that should be all right
Right, and we and we've dealt like with different different cultural
views on this and different, you know, when people, like when the life expectancy was 30 years old and there was like, you know,
there's less
people traveling and things like that and there's more about, you know, building up a big team to work your farm and stuff like that,
you know, so there's different societal
things that happen, you know, but
yeah, it's interesting though. Marcy, do you see a video about Long Island Auditor? Oh, okay, I heard about that thing.
What do you think, Yumi? What do you think?
Did the new Superman movie get released in the Philippines?
What do I think about it?
What do you think about what we're talking about right now?
What do you think about, what do you think about a man as a 19 year old dating a 17 year
old?
Let's say that.
Is that cool?
19 and 17.
19.
19 and 17 is no good.
It's good.
It's okay
Dating 17 it's not good. Yeah, you're saying it's not good
No, it's good
Teenagers I'm talking about teenagers
I have a, I have a nephew, um, and then it's okay. My nephew was, um, he was a freshman, I think, you know, he's like a football player and stuff, and he was dating the senior high school, you know, this girl is a senior, and he was a freshman, so he was 14, and she was 17, and so eventually he was 15, she turned 18, and then she graduated, and she left for college, and they had to break up.
But yeah, she was, she was kind of a little bit controversial, I would say, and got counseled. Not nice things, but.
No, just the kind of yeah, yeah, what do you think?
Weird I guess it's different, you know older female sometimes too
No, I'm at home
You're at home
You know
Anybody who wants to use the slightest thing against any of us is gonna latch them to anything we say
Right, I mean business. Yeah, it's fine. It's fine. No, it's like I've already been called everything you
I'm like I'm willing to like, you know
Everybody has to have this a sticker. Yo, you owe me. You listen. No, it's not mr. Easy is
Miss if anything is miss easy it's miss easy or just easy. He don't get a mister
You are he does not get a mister
You're muted, baby
You me you're muted and that's my culture calling people
Okay, yeah, but you're miss you're all right, but you're misgendering you're you know in the United States like they have that thing called
Misgendering you don't want to miss gender like
Female so you got to say Mrs. Easy miss
Exactly a miss miss easy
It's not wrong. Is that something is that is that a bad thing? I don't know. That's what she wants to be called
Miss easy. That's why, you know
That's why you zesty like easy, you know, you know, you're low zesty and stuff, you know, you don't want to be gender
I do picture I do picture a road nomad you want to see her
Does this
You got oh, oh, I thought it was weights. I thought it was weights. Yeah. I don't know. Maybe it's but I
Okay, I'll draw you mean next. I'll draw you mean next. Let's see. I love it. Thank you. Thank you very much
Oh, you're welcome. You will draw my face. Yeah, I'm drawing you
But do not tiny my eyes kind of small
You don't see
Hey, I got I got you. I got you. Okay. Hope you like it
Hey, you wanna see
Yeah, thank you
I have a
Does it work?
Yes, Miss Union Psyche, how you doing Psyche?
How you doing Psyche?
Miss Union Psyche, how are you doing?
I don't identify as a female, don't listen to him, there's defamation of character
and he might get a lawsuit.
What up, Chua?
Oh, he left. Okay. He left. Okay. So, he left. Of course, he left. Of course, he left.
He played all the drama, yeah. You know what, I came across a movie called Marcy X.
And I was wondering like did Marcy Fox?
It's Marcy X. If it is what you miss easy
My daughter don't want no problems. Oh, yeah easy to to to draw
Yeah
This guy should keep all
What time is it in Indonesia you be?
It's already 3 p.m. on to stay
You guys not sleep and even feel sleepy or you're from this
Yeah, you know I don't sleep
No, that's okay. I sleep
Wake up at 3 in the morning and watch this
That I'm off
It's not you, Mr. Sean P. I think so
Mr. Chompie
Sean P. No, it's not you. That's not you
Your voice kind of similar
Yeah, where's mr. Gotti I heard that the lyrics says that Gotti in the wheelchair like that
Yeah, did you hear that part?
Uh-huh. Well, you did you guys like that? That's good. Why did you know? I didn't
The AI wrote it here. Here's that yeah, I don't like
Oh hi
Stasky
That's hey, what's up?
How are you?
It's a woman. It's a woman. He's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a woman. It's a
You know not quite like Coldplay. Oh, he said easy something. He's zesty too. Look at him
Where
Bro
Yeah, I did you say he sent you right
Yeah
If you fall into any system, I bet you me is a freak. I'm not a freak
Freak not a freak don't he means like a freak
You called me a freak. Well, thank you. No. No, no, no, no, no, I chat from the side. Why are you guys are very
I think he means you're like a freak in the sheets. You know what I mean? Yeah. Yeah
Remember
I get it
That's why I mean there's a bad joke. Okay. No, you mean I don't think he know
He thinks you're cute.
Yeah.
I like Coldplay.
Coldplay.
I think so, aren't they like, or they're not popular anymore at least, but maybe they're around. Are they still around?
Maybe. Yeah, yeah. It's a fan.
Imagine, imagine, imagine, you know what, when uh,
I like joining people panels when I don't wearing my hijab and then I, I look like this, you know,
kind of, kind of, kind of nice experience.
You normally wear a hijab. Oh, yeah, you're Muslim
See not everyone gets to see you me like there. Yeah
So basically we're lucky to see you like this. Yeah
Yeah, this is me without a without a hijab. I
Wearing at work. I think yesterday I joined with the hijab
you guys yeah yesterday I was I was on panel and so then you that means you're not married right
because we're allowed to see you like this
I think it's fine um I don't show my you know your boobs thing no no I'm saying because we're
you know it's fine you if you i think um
it's okay well you know i'm not trying to play you by the way i'm really just talking to you
like having a conversation i'm asking a question i'm not a perfect one but i'm trying to be a good
Person with my religion. That's it. I don't I don't think you're a bad person
I just heard that like if a married woman is in front of other men like she's not allowed to show
You're married
okay princess don't expose the
wow i could not have expected the format well i look like coldplay so that's
coldplay don because you look like him thank you and i like coldplay thank you look at the stars
shining oh yeah yeah now he's going with it too much well guys I'm Indonesian I'm
half Chinese so I'm a Muslim I mean just see me as a human being it's like a
I thought you were a human being. I'm glad that you clarified that for me though, but many you know what many people
You could have been from outer space
Yeah, yeah
Well, I think that's one of the things that Saiki does extremely well is that he presents
a hub and outlet for people to just be themselves.
And you're in good company, Yumi.
We definitely appreciate you for who you are.
Thank you, you're always nice and humble.
You make it look like why are you guys complaining?
Why are you guys complaining from the side chat?
Oh, they always complain. They always.
Don't worry about the chat. Don't read the chat.
Do not read the chat.
Okay.
Walk the chat. You are welcome.
So you owe me um your husband he does he know that you you be on like open panels like this
He's a he's okay with it
It's okay
He knows that his majority man
Yeah, man and woman
I went to a certain doggy I went to mr. LD and Stephenie
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, Mr. Aldi. Okay.
That was probably an interesting
experience. Yeah, he he he he
disliked me now because some
reason, you know, flying monkeys
Aldi or LD? It sounds like she's
raised with a lot of more reason
respect.
Yeah
Okay, can I call you mr. Colt play of course
It's
My chubby my chubby dad YouTube dad
Come up here. Mr. Gotti. I know I know I went to the panel. You will show up God. He's up here God. He's there
Mr. Gotti. He's in the chat. What's up God?
You know
You like mr. Gotti, huh?
She likes mr. Gotti. I like
Awesome
Yeah, is that wrong? I like and respect people not love not like for you know having online
Relationship or dating or something it just like and enjoy the company
We have a lot to learn from you you operate from a higher level of respect than most of us do
Come up to me
Let me show you let me show you how to shut them cameras off
Stop pop me shit in the chat come up here and I turn let me turn the cameras on
I mean, don't let me turn them cameras off, but I'm gonna turn them off. Oh, you may bring yourself
I'm designing a
Merge for this hat. Oh, well, I can actually put people's pictures on the church
Damn what happened
you can't
You mean I don't know what you mean. Wait, it's just right here
The other guy too was a the dude
I forgot his name
Why my face is too big
That means move away from the screen baby pull the camera away from your face
My face is to be that's okay. I mean you're good. There's no problem with it looks like
It looks like uh, it's like what mr. Gotti
Cow cow cow bro, you want to make me broke hold on
Oh
Maybe by accident I don't think he did it on purpose because he like rogued the income crazy
There's ways I don't like the way he's looking at me that's the problem
Okay, here's my uncle. I don't wear wigs. Don't don't don't don't talk shit about me. Hello from the side chat. This is my real hair.
I got easy to block me to you Eric easy block me to I
Know you told me about about two weeks three weeks ago. He blocks you he ended up blocking me to
He saw getting in a little pressure you are he can't handle the pressure I
Am in the with the with the miss mr. Easy miss easy miss is easy
Mr. Easy
miss miss woman woman girl female bitch work easy as a man bitch no bitch
female woman wait wait boobies vagina woman you me my oh my god
You me hello
Cold place back. Oh, it's the cold place back
Are you are you from Canada or
Was he dating Gwyneth now where did I go what's going on
Mr. Gotti I met us a minute a minute a minute the focus of cold play
Can you me? Can you me what?
What are you guys complaining about me?
Nobody's complaining. Mr. Goddy. He can hear you. He can hear you. He's listening
What's the day
So what is the typical food in Indonesia, you mean? What's some typical Indonesian food?
You know what? This is funny. Wait. I have to... my nose...
Yo, tell me you report. Tell me you report.
It's kind of funny. Many of you visit, you know, you guys Bali Island.
Kind of famous for
Westerns people they are they are like, you know
like hang out in chill at the beach with the
Sunrise and then until they get them, you know, like a brown or black skin like that
It's kind of what do you like to eat? Hey, what's the typical food?
Oh, food. Which one? Western food or Asian food?
Asian food.
What do you like to eat?
I can cook fried rice. I can make dumplings.
I can cook garogado in an Asian style.
Do you make pork? Do you make pork dumplings? Pork?
We don't.
What is garogado?
Garu-garu is the fish vegetable salad, but with the peanut sauce
Garu-garu peanut peanut peanut fish salad with peanut sauce
Yeah, peanut sauce. Yeah, Garu-garu
I think I think a lot of I think many Indonesian any one of you
from
From from from from Quinn
Yeah, yeah me I'm from there
He's from there. Yeah, he's from there and in one of you came from Queen or something
I think every yeah me I came from there. I came from Quinn
Every Sunday there's a Indonesian buzzer buzzer Indonesian food
Yeah
You have to face it's always there you will you will see about meatballs
God of God of fried rice and then
Do you have the orange chicken and satay you guys know chicken satay?
I
How about do you have the poo-poo platter?
Have what you know pull platter a poo-poo platter
Now you just know about that garu garu garu garu garu
We don't have it we don't have
No, where is the famous singer gone? Mr. Goddy.
Who's that? Who's the famous singer?
That mister. I don't know what is his name. I can read his name too.
Okay, Mr. Stay.
What's the topic? What's up, baby? I'm listening. I'm listening. No. No. No. No. Do you do you do you do you know?
Any Indonesian food in the US, you know, you have cats. Do you got cats? I
Have cats do you have cats? It's a question. Yes. Yeah, I have
But they're stray cats
How many two
All right, um, can I hear you like your impression of one kid? Can you meow like a cat?
I just want to hear your best like impression
of a cat
No, you don't have to you know, you don't have to do it if you don't want to
I've seen there. Don't must be bored with this and don't say that.
Mr. Psyche, do you feel, are you, are you, am I boring in the sleepy head out there so?
Mr. Psyche.
Mr. Psyche said you're borrowing him to sleep? Nah.
He said that?
Really?
No, you said that. I'm saying did he say that?
No
You mean he he
Help me miss it easy
Miss you keeps you keep miss gender in her it's miss easy
No, but he's gone through the the transitioning process to be a woman
So you came this gender like there's that's like it's disrespectful
He's trying to be a woman so like you got to let him go through that like and and
Accept his nonsense and call him by a like a female, you know her she
Miss you know
Hmm oh
You think I'm joking. I'm not joking. I'm being so serious
Why you why you why you this way this like are you just like him?
Mr. Easy. Why? No, I know I'm just trying to correct you in case you didn't know.
Mr. Easy. He goes by a woman. He goes by a she he he goes by a woman now. No.
What you mean? No. When was the last time you talked to him?
Her or whatever you want to call it him her she was like when was the last time you talked to that?
I think today and he never told you that he wants to be the she like he never told you
No, she told everybody else
I respect his decisions to be a female like that's it
I
You'll never know
Did he go always send someone over mr. Gotti mr. Gotti
Mr.. Psyche
Am I boring what is the main sport of Indonesia? They what is the main thing?
What are people like into as far as sports?
I'm gonna say I'm gonna say soccer
Hmm
Yeah
Why why why English pronunciation like Batman? Oh
Badminton badminton badminton, okay badminton are you told me
badminton, badminton, and the football, badminton, and the football, I'm going to copy, isn't
Gari a huge fan of badminton, Mr. Gari, Mr. Gari.
It's my it's my chubby
You did that
Okay, that you're right that seat right there. He that is a mister. You're right. God. He is a
God he's a man me and me and mr. God is like a Tom and Jerry
That's cool. That's okay, but that is a man and
He refers to himself as a female. That's a woman
No, it's the easiest school. He always
He always respect me, and I respect him. I didn't say she wasn't cool. I just say it's not a heat
Batman
I know it's the easy don't worry. No one can bring watching me. I came for a piece
Don't worry miss miss easy. I respect you. I know me
What is happening?
Sorry my phone actually
Mr. Robe you or are you okay?
Yes, sorry. I have my my phone just
You sound so sleepy me
The one thing that I really hate the most is when many people underestimate about me.
Because you're respectful.
Because I'm trying to introduce my country, Indonesian food and the culture.
Mr. Jimmy
Well, I think that's part of putting yourself out there like they
Supposing a level of vulnerability
And we have to take everything Miss Piggy Miss Piggy. Why are you barking?
Miss mr. Where's my where's mirrors mr. Go over is mr. Coldplay
Bring him back to society
He's not just saying doesn't he have a concert to play
Yeah, they went I think the last year I think
Yeah
And he traveled with them he traveled with them, right?
a part of mr. Coldplay he traveled with them
Where's the dress exactly easy? Where's the dress? Easy's wearing a fucking dress
I knew he said it like a stream or two ago. He was like, you know I'm coming out guys and
Um, just accept me for ym and you know, he had the long hair or you know with his nipples out
And I remember that like he said
Yes biggie stop complaining about my eyes
I know the way you look miss biggie
Don't let me don't let me expose the way the the way the real you
Supposing you mean who the fuck you suppose it a
Hater
Like I'm like the enemy
I'm
Miss is buddy with flirty diamond yo easy is friends with flirty
Diamond dusty dirty diamond. You are oh my god image. It'll make sense now
It'll make sense
He see talk you into being he see like that's crazy
How do you let that happen my guy?
Yeah, holy shit, come on. Let's stop it. That was good. I like I'm mad. I ain't thinking that I'm mad. I ain't think of it
I like it
It's a big girl listen listen. I'm a bomb on you if you keep saying mr. Easy. It's a sheet
You say Mrs. Easy or just easy alone if you say mr. One more time I
Promise you it's gonna be on you from here into the end of the string
I'm not trying to be mature making me want to be like don't do it. Don't do it. Don't be my next haters. Okay. I don't want I told you
I respect all of you when you but I'm trying to tell you that he like that that easy person is gonna be very upset if you keep misgendering him her
Her I'm sorry her
If you keep saying that like she is going to be tight
All right, you know what keep saying mister keep saying
It's a man is a man
That wants to be a woman. So what do you say to that?
Except for who they are
He doesn't have a woman's voice. No, you don't understand that it listen to me
if he says publicly
He wants to be a female. He is transitioning into being a female in today's society
You have to accept it no matter what to respect that we have to accept and respect it. It's a woman now
Don't I'm trying to put you me on game, but like you meet nah, she keeps disrespecting old boy, and I don't want
Foxy
Mr. Izzy, I respect Mr. Roar, Roark.
She's adorable. She's fucking adorable. She's truly adorable
Listen to the way she talks oh
Stay turn this stay turn that every other word to stay turn
I respect your dedication. I just don't roll like that. Like, you know, if that was a real female, you know, I mean, maybe we could talk, but like, you know, you have to respect people's transitions. Yeah.
Yeah, good Tuesday
Yo miss easy sent love letters to dusty diamond and our whole picture pause super pause
Crazy
That's gonna make region. All right, Marcia. You're out, baby. Have a good one. All right, Pace
Yo, God, he blew up
God he blew easy a kiss goodnight
I'm sure she appreciates it.
Yeah, of course she does, of course.
She's a good girl. She's a good girl.
Sometimes that bitch could get out of, you know, get out of line.
You gotta smack her up a little bit, you know what I mean?
Make her fall back in line, you know.
She tends to be feisty here and there.
But as long as you keep her in line, she's a good girl.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Exactly
When she hits that time of the month
Yeah, just listen just falling line bitch that'll be the best thing for you
I
Don't care if it's that time of the month that time of the year you feeling froggy leap all that kind of bullshit
Just hold it suppress it
Suck it up. It is what it is
Sit then take it
Like a good little bitch that's it
She doesn't understand it sleep tighten is easy you are
What happened to you me you mean you meet Ben bounce she been bounce
So interesting that she's from the future
Yo, once this shit gets dead, I think got you come up. Yeah, matter of fact, I think he's coming up now
Well, oh
See what's going on in here? So we drop what's his name?
Rogue rogue broke some
You lost the road you gained a gun. We see even trade
Don't you keep it a one I
Was just gonna tell it a like on button like the first two
and now she leaves
what the fuck
I don't think you're ready, man
I don't think you're ready for what's under there
listen, I'll take the chance
I'll take the chance
that's kind of took a chance, lost two fingers, man
listen
you know
she got piranha teeth, man
Like what the fuck you doing? Where are you psych? Yeah, what are you doing? Well, you lying under the covers man. Just watching this shit
We'll just phone under the covers or snuggled up and shit and making sure nobody got
PB's and he's got a snuggly on he just all fucking comfortable under the fucking
Make sure he lets the right people up here. Uh-huh. Yeah, just in case he doesn't want to fall asleep with
Yeah, we'll let a whole fucking porno play out before we're like, oh, yeah, yeah, we'll
let the whole thing play out.
You see that shit that happened the other day, he let, he had Athens up here with Ziggy.
It was like four hours, they just kept talking back and forth.
And that was they got a bomb Isaiah was buttoning around the conversation. It was like a four-hour fucking conversation
They got bombed or something or not. No, they just stayed up here the whole time
Until our Athens dropped up by accident. No
Wasn't here for that one. I wasn't here. How the fuck can you talk about shit for four hours? What the fuck?
Yeah, I don't know I have no idea
Shit, I remember me me and you was backstage. We was backstage one time and we talked for like shit less than five minutes
And we you know, we was out like that. You know
I'll meet you here, I'll meet you there. I see you here. See you there. That's it. It's done. Come on
Yeah, see you on the next one captain. That's all, you know, we were we were capping on Monica. I remember that
that's the one you put the link with, you was like check out this fast slob, is that the one you put the link in, you was like check out this fast slob, you and Justin bore you
I
Yeah, so I'm in the wrong conversation right now. Thank you me. What's up, baby?
Where you've been where you've been doing
Why you got that bitch face watch the mix smeared. Yeah, why are you so mad? Oh
She's not happy look at that. She's a she looks miserable
You me you me why is your lipstick smeared fix your microphone? I can't hear you you mute it
Hello, you'll meet at the arm you fun, baby. Mr. You me. It's me mr. Gotti
She's got a bad signal she's lagging you're lagging you're ragging
oh that's not a good angle
is she talking in slow motion?
you and me are lagging
the wi-fi
there you go there you go that's better
yeah what are you doing
the wi-fi
Hey, but why are you so close to the camera?
You make a new meow for me. Can you meow do a meow?
Little kitty cat meow meow meow do it meow
Do it
You could do it baby. Come on. Come on. Do it. Do it
Do it DSL's on came do it for God
Yo, let us get one. Yeah, come on. Don't be shy. I
Hate you wife. I
You got the you got the cat teeth and everything like we can see a little point on the canine. It's like
Just give us a little one
Just give us a little
Come on you can do it. You know you want to do it
Why you call yourself cat and you don't want to do it
Come on, give me cat
What kind of cat are you
Doing good
Are you like a house cat or like a wild cat you
What's that noise in the background sounds like somebody's doorbell
Her husband saying hello
He's praying right now.
Oh shit, she did it I didn't hear it. Fuck. Well, he did it do it again
No, she can't do it during prayer
Give me some fucking food
Somebody ghost. Oh, yeah, there we go. There we go
Do it again. Now you said it. It sounds like. Oh, that's good. I like that. Oh my god
That's good. Keep doing that. Yeah. Yeah, dude. Do it like five more times. I'm almost there
I'm happy they don't stop every girl should do that on panel once they get up here just
not just me a little bit except for Amanda Amanda we don't want you to do that don't
That's that's amazing. Oh shit. You'll meet one more time. Oh my. Uh-huh. Yeah. Oh
You just killed my shit
You we think I just say meow
Uh-huh. Yeah. Yeah. Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Keep going, baby. Keep going.
I'm edited. Every kind of cat.
What kind of show is this?
I like lions. I like...
Yeah, do more. Do more. Do more.
Do the lion. Do the lion.
I like everything.
You look like a retarded Jason Statham. What are you talking about?
No, it's not. Don't say that.
No, no.
Come on.
Who's saying that?
Yeah
No, that's not that's not allowed don't say that
Psychi doesn't want any religion on here
Beetlejuice, what do you mean psyche is the team move Howard stir?
That's like that's not even fun again like that's corny is out like that's why
He's a team
He ain't trying to be no damn how it was starting stupid
Allah, who I bet
bar
Allah snack bar. I did it Sigati. You're not allowed to say that stuff
Only men are allowed to pray they said
As long as you get on your knees and pray to God
You're very worthy. You just got to get on your knees like that's that that's the first step
So any type of like praise you get on your knees any type of praise
You know God is God, right? Say it. You mean God is God
God is God said
You know you want to say it just say it say it
God he's God you me
Listen to how similar the name sound God II God
Like God like so yeah, just just just say it God he is God one time
this day yeah why why
i'm gonna be your enemy i'm gonna be your enemy turn you ever see turn you ever see the golden child
the golden murphy
Oh with the the the the the the Chinese boy, right? The little kid. Yeah
He's baby picture looks just like that dude. No for real man, you'll be show your baby picture
No, you me got a baby picture on here stop
I mean if you want to show it you me if you want me to show it
Looking like Avatar the last airbender and shit
She's the chosen one
She loves it see
Just say it's a meow meow that's a meow
Matter of fact easy come up easy come up here. Say meow what I think easy what to sleep
All right, she would say a better easy would say a better than you you chase them out. She would say you're more feminine
All right, taste the mouth she bounce he yeah, she bounced I had to go
Take care of some feminine shit
He's so sensitive man, what the fuck you know, you know women know what you guys
This is all before I came to TPP in this place man, you guys must have really fucked them up
Yeah, you know this is wrong. You know
There's some room
Well, he's got psyche now, that's good
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's like you take care of nicely psyche you take care of
You fell asleep man this this we control the panel now, you know that hey, yeah, whatever everything goes through us now
We need some bitches up here though, what do we got? Yeah? Yeah, thank you who we got
Yeah, look they come back
Let me see who we got we got Liz we got Liz down there. She's not a bitch though. Come on up Liz
We got a fake gaudy down there
What's the picture though? Oh, yeah, I see
Oh, okay.
Yeah, the gate is cool.
Who the fuck is gay?
Some big fat homo.
Hey, um, a site.
If you're awake, get rid of that
Gotti in the chat.
That's not that's not real
Gotti.
I got to handle that.
Myself.
Hold on. Can you do it from up? Can you do it from here? I could take care. Hold on
States her looks like be it'll juice from you know
It's better. I can't do it. Motherfucker got me blocked
You me mm-hmm sing for me
Sing for me
What sing a song baby sing a song
Mr.. Gotti what what kind of song okay? I will sing a song that's sweet
No, I don't want to sing
You don't want to sing
You could sing a loud bar just just singing every night sexually. You know, I mean like
It still won't work not that song and nobody want to hear that
Don't say that. Don't say that
Whoa, whoa, whoa, who's putting who's putting the swastikas in the room? What's the fuck is going on?
Don't be don't be so rough. The room's out of control. I don't
Don't be tonight. Should I sing this song?
Yes, I don't play it though. Don't play it
Just sing it. No, no, I don't wait. Oh
I'm using my Chromebook and the Wi-Fi is, it's not...
It don't matter, you sound great, you sound great, sing, just sing.
No, I'm not gonna sing.
Yeah, sing what?
Oh yeah, sing what? You aren't singing what?
Give me things, what grade?
Sing what?
WAP.
WAP?
Yeah, yeah, why why you know wet ass pussy wet
Yeah, sing it you
You I won't do that. I won't do that. Do you say you?
You
What is it like you're gonna sing dry as because mr. Stake it's saying a pushy
Dad
Let me hear that again
That's why he's he mentioned about a pussy, I don't know because maybe maybe Mr. Stay don't have don't have a girlfriend
That's why that's why he's he mentioned about a pussy
I don't wear
Look type in your little Google box on party be wet
Like it ain't you carry the world on your back look at you
Keep going. I want to keep going baby. There's another verse.
The light, your face, a pine, it's floating like fireworks in the sky.
You don't know that song. Do you know that song?
I'm exploding. Why are you singing it? Keep going, keep going.
He's almost done
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, I like I like this part. Oh, you keep teasing me. Stop it girl. Stop playing with me. I
Don't I don't
Okay, then
Welcome to Dictie Education.
Okay, that's it.
I will switch off the Chromebook.
Okay, what's next?
Alright so what's next is next time you see the the the the easy person you got to say miss
easy because that person wants to be identified as a
female
Why you hate mr. Easy
I don't hate it. I don't hate it. Why are you calling it?
Why are you calling it? It's not a male. It's not a female.
Because he does not want to be called.
He does not want to be called him anymore. He wants to be called a her, a she, a female.
No.
How do you know? How do you know, Miss Yumi?
That was rubbish Jimmy
You know, I'm you know, I'm his next door neighbor. You know, I'm his next door neighbor
Did you know that I'm his I'm the next door neighbor
No, I'm not I'm telling you I'm his next door neighbor. He wants to be a she right now
So you gotta say miss easy you must hear a moan every day
Who's Beedlejuice from the the Howard Stern show the
No, I think it's ghost
Oh, oh when the chat
Now somebody earlier says something about um Beedlejuice from the Howard the Howard Stern show
That's the you know the dude. Okay. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, he's from my area. Yeah
Not bad for a crackhead, baby
Yeah, yeah, he was funny as hell like he was funny
Not a pedophile don't say that who said that
What that? Who is I don't know George?
Oh George Wallace from the site cat. Oh
Hey page. It's a guy page is here. You me. She's gonna read for you
You you need a reading you me page. Can you read for you? Yeah? Yeah quick?
We got a swastika in the fucking chat. What the fuck is dropping these dropping loads on the fucking chat?
The joy. There's no other mods out there that can take you George Wallace George Wallace
Yo, there's any
If there's any mods up here right now, take care of your own George Wallace. You are
Mr. Gotti I met I met I met a vocalist of Coldplay
From this panel. Oh, you made a vocalist from Coldplay really where?
But from from this paddle he looks like he looks like him who what was the name I
Don't know let this day. What is his name? I don't know I can oh he's talking about
Just up here about like 20 minutes ago. Yeah, cool. Mr. Stay talking about who I think he's talking about rogue
No mad rogue no matter the other guy
Oh dry. Oh, she's coming about the guy that was up here earlier. Yeah, I think he's talking about that dude
She's talking. Oh, yeah, that was on broke. Yeah
He's a guy from no
Yeah, the other one dad of one doesn't that's not mr. Rogue. Yeah, the one
There was nobody else up here. It was me you and him
And they got me my missus thank you still with us when missus bike is still with us
of this is the second the middle of the
that was wrong, Mr. Roe
not one
that before Mr. Gotti come up here
after that I will rewind it
I will rewind
Mr. Gotti
Will, will, will you help me, will you help me, uh, about Mr. Sensitive?
Um, if, if he start, you're, you're, you, you have your...
Friends and I hope if miss sensitive start to disrespect me
Well, your time came out like a 10 seconds or she's working on she wants you to fuck with Lord Vader. Oh
Yeah, yeah, yeah, he's not here
Yeah, he's so his he was mad at me he's mad at me
It seems like you're kind of mad at him
Is that no he mad at me
Way is is that a sir Billy?
Sir fat Billy sir Billy Hayden
He's not a normal one. You know that way white trying to be black
Fatso get up here
You throw around allegations like that get up here. Yeah, you fat bitch. Mm-hmm. Yeah, you fat bitch
What the fucking donut down and get up here
Who we talking about fat Billy
Goes by Hayden you see his name in the chat sissy Hayden
this is he Hayden let me see
Billy Hayden
he Hayden
oh god he the vietnam vet the vietnam oh that's what he keeps saying
yeah he's one of those his special needs
does he does he sound like he could have even been in that war like like think logically like
Does his voice match a 70 year old man? I
Was special forces Billy your special needs
Yeah, yeah, I mean he must have been in the Vietnam War when he was fucking five, you know
Song you be sing that
Sing it.
Comey
Comey comey you mean my bag
I'm just in I could be
That's your mom's favorite song you can call me daddy
What's your favorite song you don't have
You guys to do it. Go ahead. I won't say anything. Go ahead. You have a nice voice. You have a nice voice. Yeah
You have a nice voice keep singing I want to hear
Get your mom and your peers so me and her could do the like we could do the whole duet
She could do one part. I could
Yeah, like that
Somebody else's channel and they fell asleep like this
This place would be fucking chaos it would have went to shit like an hour. Oh so fast. We would have been shut down in five minutes
You can trust us like we're not up here putting porn up here and playing fucking music playing movies
Talking racist shit making threats. We're not doing that
Yes, did you did you so?
Great already you like 15 for all of you. I think so. Yeah, it's like 15th. What's July 15th?
Not today is it yeah, but what are we celebrating?
What's so special about your life
What's so special about your life at 10th? That's what he's saying. No, yes. No yesterday
Yesterday is July 14. Yeah, what is it? Mr. Aldi birthday?
No, he says it's not he says the 28th
So it's another oh, I like that I mean this is being alive
I'm in this of being alive. That's a good one. That's a good one. What's that mean?
She we were saying was like July 15th or 14th. She said she said being alive. That's a good one. That's a good one. I
don't get it. Oh
Not because we was talking about what we celebrate
I get it.
That was pretty good.
Being alive is good.
Oh hi Miss Linda.
It's good on July 15.
July 15 is special.
Good for you.
Linda.
Linda, listen Linda.
Linda, why is your life
so special Linda?
I want to hear from Linda. Why is Linda? Why so special?
Yeah, yeah, tell us baby. Why is July 15th so special?
We're all in baby girl. We want to have her
She's gonna say it's our birthday. Yeah, you don't you don't want to call you don't want to call Linda baby girl. Trust me
I
Trust me trust me
Are you sure is ms. Linda you mean
Happy birthday, Miss Linda.
Suckie Suckie, fall out of there.
Happy birthday, Happy Birthday, Happy Birthday, Miss Linda.
I'd expect that from her.
You know, we knew that she needed classy.
That was classy.
Oh, shit.
Is it McLinda from Miss Zenny? I think.
Yomi, I thought you know. That's her, yes.
Mr. Stachan, Stachan.
I haven't seen Zenny in a while.
Miss Yomi, have you ever worked in a...
In a metropolis?
Yomi.
Yomi, Miss Yomi.
Yes, yes, so I'm gonna do my damn home or whatever you say. Um
Yeah, yeah, all right
Have you ever worked in a mustahs parlor?
What
Miss Yumi. Have you ever worked in a massage parlor? Yes or no? Like, did you? Yumi you do massage
Rubbing tugs, you know, like the whole shebang Yumi you do long time. I
Don't get it. What is what is the question? I don't have you ever worked in a massage parlor
Okay, have you ever gave massages to men that paid for massages? Yes or no?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I just I just do it for my husband. Oh
You do my dad. Oh
Oh
Okay
You okay, um happy happy endings and happy ending too. Is he happy afterwards?
What do you mean happy ending?
that's your father
I don't I don't live with my dad anymore
No, but when you give your father eight eight hours from me
Eight hour missile. You give him an eight hour massage. Wow
Holy shit
I would give you like fucking
$300 for eight hour
I said that I don't live with my dad anymore.
I know, but you said you give him eight hour massage.
No, I live far from him.
Oh, so you're saying you live eight hours away?
Oh, gosh, you gosh.
Can you find another question?
Why about, why about my dog?
You get feedback
Who me are
What do you mean?
What are you trying to say?
You're a jerk.
Why?
Why? What did he do to be like deserved like being called a jerk?
Yeah, why you call me a jerk?
Now I'm just kidding.
Oh, now you're just kidding?
You have
No, not me
It's a mr.. Gaudi they call the body
What a blonde
About time it showed up. What's up? Yeah, what's up, Nicky? How you doing?
Nicky's got a new man now. She's like to show off her picture with a new man. Oh Nicky's a woman
What's up, Nicky?
Nicky's a man
Yeah, miss Nicky C is a woman, but Nicky is a man
She says what a woman emoji with her hand raised up like Gotti. Can I speak now? Um Gotti? Hello. Hello. Look at me
Can I talk?
She has her hand raised like a good
Yes
That is Nikki's picture, okay
I would I would definitely try a goth chick at least one time in my life. I would definitely
Oh, yeah, I'm about to say because our face doesn't look bad.
No, that's not me.
That's not me.
We know that's not you.
You're me.
Damn.
Believe it.
We know that's not you.
You're...
No, the echo.
The echo is you.
Okay.
See?
Is that for me?
No.
Oh, I see my shit lighting up.
Hold on.
Oh Mr. Stay, it's you.
Oh shit, it was you.
Stop slandering me.
It's from Mr. Stay, not from me.
Sorry, sorry, you got that good equipment.
Sorry.
I forgive you Chubby Dad.
I always forgive you.
But you're always disappointed.
Thank you Chubby Girl.
I'm sad.
You're very chubby one.
Am I?
Yeah.
Really?
You're like a dumpling.
You're like a chubby dumpling.
Dumpling.
Dumpling is white.
Dumpling is white, not a chubby.
Yeah, well you're white.
Your face is a little white.
Wow.
But I'll be yellow.
Yeah, I know you're yellow.
You're yellow flower.
I'm so proud be a yellow Indonesian
email
Anyway, how are you mr. Gotti? I'm okay. I'm just hanging in there, you know
Trying to live in this fucking crazy world. You know, I'm so I'm glad that when you're not
being around with
Can I say the NPD and my one gives you you you kind of you kind of nice and
You let me tell you something I'm always nice
Everything I do is nice if you always nice if you always nice why you block me why you always if you I told you
You were rambling in the chat. All you do is ramble and it got boring
Well, it's a shaggy why you were dumb things I
Know oh
Shit, he's still awake a page
I don't know if he has ever seen her miss page because he has kind of addicted with the blondie woman like you
Just because I made the I love spring rolls
Me too, man, that's their ball. Yeah, right they come in clutch right dumplings are great
Like all the whole the whole thing. Oh, yeah, you've done things. You've done things are my favorite
Yo, state your steak roses popping on steak roses. It's like number one
You got steak rolls then egg rolls then spring rolls
Solid roll with like that's got like the fresh like make this is basil. It's like it's Vietnamese
and it's got the vermicelli noodles and it's got carrots and all the stuff in it and then it's got
shrimp usually and it comes with that peanut sauce yeah i never had that i don't know that
i don't need siku but is that a batagor? is that a batagor? batagor with the peanut sauce?
no gado gado? i think that's what you call it but i call it a spring or a salad roll
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
God, oh god, oh really soft
So the last day who are you because you said that I know you but I don't know you
Yo, who's playing on a xylophone in the background? That's me. The wind
Yeah, man, it sounds like a xylophone every time
I gotta play this
I'm trying to get her back to the roots
I'm eating Arab
Arab what
You mean is that is that what is it?
It's garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu garu gar
Hello page you got a meow every girl that comes up. Yes, the meow
There we go
Bravo, bravo, baby. It was great. It's not a fool
That was perfect. You heard
Oh like this like they when the cat start the start the fight
How is it that sound? No, no, it's not like that
Well, your name is you know cat do it you me do you meow?
This guy name this is me. No, no, I will not do that
Yes, you will not do that. You will do that. You'll do it right now
You're going to do it. You're doing it. You're gonna do it right now right meow God commands you right meow
I
Can you can you're doing it when you're not on the spot you mean do it then like you'll think you want later
And just like throw it at us like randomly. Yeah, just do it out of nowhere. Like
That's the best way to do shit like that, right? Just like
Spontaneous
Exactly font newity with your meows
You me do the lion
She does a great lion
Now she's shy she gets a little shy sometimes
It's okay raw for me one time, baby. Well, just roll one time on you me
There you go
Rara, Rara, Rara, Rara, Rara, Rara, Rara, Rara, Rara, Rara, Rara, Rara, Rara, Rara, Rara,
It's not like too many men
Good I love hearing I love that for you. Thank you. You're welcome. How's work? It's good. It's good
And I baked it I baked a cake like after hours tonight at the clubhouse
We also went golfing me my co-worker after it was raining all day
And then as soon as it stopped raining because our boss said we don't have to work all day if we don't want to because it's
pissing rain and
So as soon as the rain stopped like fuck it glock this bitch up. Let's go golfing
So we went out golfing in like a little bit of the rain and it was super wet.
Oh, but we did some of the best.
I'm getting so much better.
And so is my co-worker.
So anyways, there's some growth there.
So that part was good.
And um, but also they do we baked.
I baked a cake because tomorrow is one of, uh,
we have a birthday.
Yeah.
A person that's coming in for a birthday tomorrow.
And so I baked this cake and then I'm going to do a maple chocolate marble swirl fucking popping like a
Icing there we go
I will I will take a picture and I'll put it. I don't know. I guess on my YouTube. I'll be sick
Right. I love this that you haven't so much fun at this job man. This is awesome
Yeah, Jason before golfing is life honestly that's like we have so much fun here, but we're also like we work really hard
I work really hard so my we all do right we work hard and we get to play hard too
We're respected and so we get the freedom right and we're trusted as well. That's the best thing
Yeah, I love that that we can just like go out golfing and and honestly we do earn it
We do earn it for sure, but they're very laid-back
So so my boss will like seasonal right it's gonna be seasonal. Yeah close up to locked about late October
Thing but like we have like go was it glow golf so we do it in the night
And when we have glow sticks inside these clear golf balls, so you have a gleave a nighttime glow tournament twice
in the season and then I'm doing a blow up movie theater like I have a big outside screen
that's a blow up movie theater it's for that
And I'm gonna do like movie night at the golf course
And then we'll do like popcorn and drinks and stuff like that and then do everybody like in wow yours outside
And we do a bunch of events like we do you know bachelors parties birthdays
Like we just make it fun, right? We didn't have to bake a cake, but like fuck we were just hanging out at the clubhouse anyways
So my co-worker lives here in the like the camp area, right? She's like the main watch so
She's like you're so kind
Yeah. She's like my manager. My boss is great too. She always is like, oh, it's ladies night. We can close up early. Let's go golfing. I'm like, okay.
Wow. That's cool. Yeah, so fun.
Do they have special functions in the winter?
Um, we, they, okay, so they tried to, uh, last year and the year before, but the people that, one of the ladies that was trying to run it was just, uh, it's not, she was an adequate and it kind of failed.
So it's harder to see a small town out here too, and it's like we live in hard winter, right?
Oh
So just coming out
Traveling out here and and honestly most people are pretty like hermity in the winter time here either that or they're taking care of their farm
You know, so it's isolated. Okay. It's a little bit isolated. Yeah, it's not like a really bougie one either
so it's just kind of
Good people to come from all over the place to be here and everybody comes here for an experience
But it's not it's because it's laid back and it's because of the experience, right?
I thought it was like a like a country club setting
No, it's not that bougie. It's still a golf course in a country club, but it's not like high-end super high-end, right?
It's not a million dollars. No, I could see why they wouldn't have functions in the winter and stuff. Okay. Yeah
No, but I mean most golf courses around here, even if they are a little bit higher end
It's like these shut down during the winter time
Anyways, they don't stay open because the only thing you would be able to offer is the kitchen and booze which is
People are gonna stay in town for that, right?
What about skiing over there? They must be like a skiing resort or something. Yeah, there is it's um not
It's about an hour away from me where the first one is and then the other ones are more like in the mountains
So they're a little bit further away
You have to try
Yeah, I can imagine the winters up there being nasty
We did do like some cross we did used to have like cross country skiing and snowshoeing and like sledding and stuff
Are there any Inuit tribes up there?
Inuit tribes?
Yeah, a little further up. I'm not here. Oh, you're not that high. Okay
Yeah, I always wondered how low they come
You always wondered what I was wondering how low like how far down the Inuit tribes come
I know they're up in Alaska stuff like that
Didn't know how far down they come
They come as far as like yellow knife. Oh
My gosh, you got the whole thing of balls and teas on the ground. Oh my gosh
balls and cheese
Like golf teas and balls we were just me my co-worker at her trailer right now and sorry she's having a cock
She's been sick in the hospital. She's older, lady.
Anyway, so she's just dropped a whole bunch of balls and tees on her feet.
Are you okay?
Oh, yeah.
You're good, okay.
They come off my...
Cue the Heimlich.
Well, no, she had cancer, right?
So she's just, and she had pneumonia really bad.
So she's just not recovered from it.
And like, it's really damp here right now, and so it's cold.
Oh, yeah.
So it's definitely affecting her.
You're so rude Paige. Oh, wow Kim, okay
Why am I rude? He's literally right here instead of herself. I said I'm not dead yet. Oh
Wow, I
Would never go to Canada because I think they're weird
Wow the chat's really nice the Canadians today, oh, it's fine. It's fine. Can you is our fucking weird and Canada is weird
Yeah, I'm nothing that's not even a it's fine
It's all about positive thinking with cancer that's about 50% of the battle
Here she's listening listening I beat it so far there you go see it's positive. Yeah
I'm always positive. There's no point in negativity. That's true leaving it
No, even even a healthy person can succumb to negativity. That's right. Yeah
Yeah, if you believe in it, I don't
Well, so you know when you go through those kinds of things that you have to learn you learn how to be positive always
It's a choice. Yeah, it is. Yeah, I always say that because everyone's always so mad about positivity page
And I'm like, you know what? I'm not like I'm light and dark and that's the thing
It's like it's a choice because I know everybody's going through things and like why would I be the person to push everybody lost
The ledge why wouldn't I help you off it if I could you know is um, but sometimes it's fun to fucking roast
I'm nothing sometimes it's fun to cook, but it's just like there's a time and a place, right?
Yeah, this stuff is read very easily around here. Yeah, I try not to play into it, you know
No, I try to be positive. Oh says the one that's a moderator in my channel. Do you guys you would I hate negativity?
What are you even talking about and I don't even know what you're talking about. Mm-hmm. We were spreading cheer
We were spreading cheer and joy pagey
That's good, it was fun that got weird later though. Hey like my I don't like
No, never mind. We're not gonna say it.
No, no. Go ahead and say it.
Some of the, like...
Some of the critters that are drawn into the to my like to the lives later in the night
They're all from a specific place. Mostly. Yes
Fucking weird. Oh, you got it. It's weird. Oh, no, it's a rape culture up there. It is not cool, dude
Yeah, it's not it's hard. It makes me not
It makes me it made me I had to look like not one I know certain times now not to be on live
But that's also not fair for me to have to say
I was like I can't be on live at this time anymore because of this I think that they just need to
wrangle up some of that like lock it up you know you're gonna block them out that's all I just
don't read every comment no but then they start saying they can start getting mad about it that's
like fuck them I don't care I think we handle it well yeah I'll talk like fuck them fuck them
that's why you got Jamie's there to handle that stuff
Um, well, yeah, there's lots of people there that are doing it though, like, you know
I can only do what I see
All my mods are wonderful in their own way
They all do their job in their own way that they see fit and I that diversity that makes it kind of
Not one per like you're not getting kicked out or like, you know timed out or deleted for one thing
It's just like, you know, if somebody sees fit then they see fit, right? If it's offensive, it's offensive. It's not it's not
And you guys are pretty good with what you know, that will bother us. Same with psych too. You know, you trust people to
We wouldn't be mods if people didn't trust us to do so at our own discretion, right?
Was Justin being offensive yesterday? No, no, no, no, not you guys. I don't know. What do you mean? No, not you and Justin
I'm just saying like those random people and you know who I mean
You know what I mean, there's a lot of strange business
They're like months to a flame. They see a blonde girl up there. They go nuts
Well, I have to do I have to dye my hair. That's why I put this picture up
Yeah, also, I was gonna say what's with your fucking little avatar. It's positive people
It looks like that Megan doll slash like a golf it does look like her like a golf version. Yeah
Now they stick to see in my face, so I thought I'd change it up
I'll have a nice sleep Amanda
Hi, Irby.
Yo, Irby.
In the chat, yeah. She's like, what are you still going to do? I'm like, just we're just addressing the chat.
Paige, Cyclic, you're up here, right? Yeah, why wouldn't you let me up here? No, I'm just saying. I thought I thought he was sleeping.
I thought he was sleeping too. Cyclic, are you awake? I want to talk to you about those songs.
You had a big meal tonight. That's why he's in a coma. Is that like 45 fish tacos or what? No, no, no
Take restaurant or something like that with his family. Oh, yeah, like he had some red meat in his diet
So he's gonna have a little he's having a steak coma or what? Yeah, he's he's knocking out. He probably has some cheese cake
Oh you mirror welcome for whatever, okay, what's going on this time?
She's thanking us for something. I don't even know what
Nicky you out
All right, Nicky. Take care
Ignore with your new man, Nicky. I
Hope you treat you well
If he doesn't treat you well, you know what to do just stab him in the side
Well, we can't say that up here shit
It's like you playing Wizard of Oz tonight, what's that mean?
You guys see those birds?
Oh, it's me. Oh, shit.
Yeah, don't worry Amanda. We got everything under control.
I don't think it was in the center standing because I said, um, what's going on in the chat?
And she said, no, it's under control. No, I know it is. I just thought that there was something going on because there is a
It's my bad.
Page balances me out. See if I was up here by myself would be chaos
There he is
Did you hear the song yet though?
Which one yeah, there weren't gaudy in it. I'll put go I really like did you send those three that I really liked or no
I'll post them. I'll post them on me. See I think
Yeah, this is good. Hold on. Is you like it through your ass? Yeah, I'll see how it is. Hold on. Let's see. I just use this one
I'm not sure though. Hold on
I'd be this one crazy night Nicky
Oh
I'm dancing on the table like conspiracies don't die
Be the sippin' wine and let her ex
Top's gone flying, it's a certified mess
She's spilling all the tea, now that's a fire
That's my cat and her farts gone viral
Woke up handling the rules to this
If you're saying turn back, you will not be missed
Since the media has got it, you'll look like this
It's proving me out that it looks like your thing is like a horror version of me and Gaudi, and you know you've seen that.
What, my pick?
Yeah.
Hold on.
I think my pick is terrible too.
Did you just say it's harder than you?
Yep.
I know, I know, I know, I sucked out of these, just like kept looking at them, like is that true of me?
Like it's just like the contrast of the corner of my eye or whatever like first step.
Like nope, no, no, no, no.
Can you hear the song?
No, I can't.
Oh, explain.
No, can't hear nothing.
Can you hear it?
I can hear it. It's like loud.
What's my problem?
I don't know.
Oh, jeez.
Good grief. I'm hearing a different person.
It's pretty good. I like the beat.
Well, it's not... I can't hear it.
Where is it?
Perhaps... Wait, who's doing this to me?
I think you're in it.
No, I feel like I probably hit it, but I can't hear it.
I didn't hear my part yet
I can hear any of them in a bit. I heard those songs earlier.
Do I have to like, leave the panel? No. Just hear it. No, don't make this.
He's just a fish taco
In a world on fire.
He has made, so there was like three songs earlier that I was supposed to play.
He's been playing them making little jingles all night, but...
There's three of them that I'd like
This was the best one so far
I think he's replaying it
Yeah, he doesn't replay it
Oh boy, still can't
It's like being a fetal flash flash flash
Oh, that one? Okay
Is it from earlier?
Might have a new beat to it
Either way
Who's complaining about a wreck?
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
Oh, sir, just stuck out.
Starts a feud in the comments nonstop stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress stress
Sharp like tarot, sweet like sun, rolls her eyes, zips her tea, brings the heat with sarcasm, glee.
Down in the dark with a mole rat's crepe mini-man,
Sings him right to sleep, he howls to the moon with a bluesy sting,
Tarot cards dance in the spirit, sing.
Jokers here with a smirk so sly, draws page's face with a spark-a-lie,
Howls to the moon with a bluesy sting, Tarot cards dance in the spirit, sing.
That's what you need, you need like a wicked beat, like that.
Yeah, that's a good one. It's too much. Oh no. Yeah, it's too much. I'm psyched. Yeah
That's Rob. That's Rob. You know
Sexy Rob. Yeah, Rob. You know Rob King Rob. Yeah, that's him. Oh good grief
Good grief
I should have known by all of the emojis. Yeah, he's an emoji freak
Well, hello Rob. What's up? Don't be don't don't be doing that though
Man he's trying to be incognito, you know, he doesn't want certain people to see what he's doing
Just in case they're watching
I exposed you Rob
Okay
This is not King Rob. No, it's not King Rob
That's what I was saying. He's not gonna admit it. No way for real is that's Vader
Bear then you watch your flippin little mouth
That's not how you talk to anybody so she me
Is it being rude what do you say?
Well, not rude just like
So little wet dream ball comments
That's fair Vader would say stuff like that though
No
Not not as himself though. He would never know quite not quite
Yeah, Liz he went to shit he looks like garbage
That's you Rizzy, for real? What are you doing talking to me like that either too?
Come on, they're out of control
Yeah, more like chip and fail
Chip and Dale my ass
So like what are you doing you guys?
I was trying to pull out this
Just I'm doing some of the pictures right now, sorry
Make it a video. No, I'm trying to like make it. You know make some like my
my
Graphics you obsessed with AI music now
No, I'm doing I'm just trying to graphics with this, but it's like it's like so kind of complicated like figuring out how to
Do everything copy. Okay. Thank God
But I can make it back. I can make a banner with like my picture on it, you know, my yeah, I put a small
It's really slow, okay
So you need to accept it
Good morning black RG
God is God
Okay, and yes hi Riz
Yo, I see what up, man
What will candles you guys don't burn candles
And do I really but
Page you're not home, right
Page page here page she wants to know where you are
Tell him, he wants to know your location and coordinates you're not going to ever know my location and coordinates and also know I'm like not still working but like we have a campground and a and so like my manager lives like in seasonally at the campground and so it's right because we're just I'm still hanging out with her.
We were by the fire earlier we went golfing and now we're just hanging out in the camper
And then I'm gonna go home in a little while and then I work later or later tomorrow evening. So
Show her six ask you what she thinks you're sick. Okay. I will
Siggum try to hook you up, bro
Yeah, I don't need it. Thank you very much
66 Ziggy
What's up and say hi after you buddy? I'm doing it. No, you're not
I know she says he looks like a young man
Oh, that's nice
Because you shave or get a haircut like what's up with you? It looks like a lot less like you're wearing a lot less going on there
I'm wearing less
Like I don't know. I'm usually shirtless
No, you're doing not usually I
Don't know what you mean by that. I mean like did you get a haircut or did you shave or something?
There's you look like a stranger
No, I still have the hair on my chin
Or whatever on my neck I see that that's definitely not your chin. Yep
Chin neck
whole region
Under my head
Let's just say under my head
Is that dangerous?
Yeah, I
Have crabs I have crabs in my my neck. We're from eating out your mother great. That's great
I'm sure pages colleague will love to hear that
Cheers oh, I care so much talk obviously the golf course is not like my career, right?
It's just I love my job and come back like so next year
I'll come back as well and these seasonal time and it's good money. It's great people. I
It's just beautiful here and it's a place of peace for me, you know
I never mind her of every day of my strength and my growth
So you can make fun of me all you want whatever but no, I'm gonna go back to school
I think that I'll probably go back in like December. I think I'll go back to school
But also you don't even know what the fuck I've done with my life
You enjoy your life and do whatever you want. No, but he doesn't nobody's gonna be nobody's gonna be there
Nobody look it doesn't matter. Look watch
Nobody's gonna be there with you when you're at the end of the line and you're winning, right?
nobody's gonna be there
While you're struggling like trying to get to the end of the line like the finish line, right?
Like these people are to have no involvement. So it does not matter what they have to say
I do by myself every single day. I know that's what I'm saying
You don't have to worry about what other people are saying they don't know no matter fuck them
I love my job. I don't know what you're gonna explain yourself to nobody. All right. See I get what you're saying
I love what I do for a living
I collect dividends
No, you work at the airport
Amazing
Say you should do tarot
Yeah
See those fucking in
You get it like super drunk just fucking pull out any card just start reading it
Then stop taking a shit in the middle of the reading
They'll pay you for that
Yeah, believe it
Marcy
Marcy come on up Marcy
Marcy's like my blankie
No way. Yeah, she keeps me warm
Beauty college
I just wasn't trying to interrupt. I was listening, right? You were talking.
God has no idea. I want to hear you guys talk.
He used to be six foot three. I don't want to say anything. I just want to listen.
But I don't want to listen to God. I want to listen to Paige.
Why am I talking?
I want to hear a page from Paige.
I don't really know what to say.
Do you have questions?
What do you want to hear?
What is the meaning of life?
Okay.
Well, that's our very own interpretation, right?
Everybody's perception of that is different for themselves
as well as everybody's outlook.
They're like their goal.
The way that they do what they do is like,
there's an understanding of what your life is meant.
your own I don't know I guess the highest self of you and like true self you
know what you guys I don't know what the fucking mean like he left he left he
left you don't have to say okay good I'm done yeah he already left you didn't give
a shit he set you up I don't care I don't care he totally set you up it's
okay fuck you Ziggy
Fuck holes get money. Oh, I hope you have a good day kind of you know, yeah, but not really
But like that's why I said kind of
half good half bad
Like you'll find $20, but he'll like fall down
You know by $20 buy a bottle of Everclear
Then we'll all worry about him and then he'll disappear for two days and then we'll see him again, you know shit himself
Professor Frank
So I could tell you the meaning of life, but you wouldn't listen. What's the point?
Don't try to test God, but I'm not here to be tested
Enjoy the ride
Yeah, Mars. Do you think you think they let him near the planes?
He's the guy that takes out the trash he empties all the garbage cans around the airport
I've seen you working there when I was flying
Yeah, you saw sick. He's wearing the math. I knew it. I knew it
Where's he live again doesn't he live in California? I
Always thought he was like in Samoa or some shit. I don't know why
Pages they want a Pokemon reading really funny Beetlejuice
You're gonna do a dark reading one night
But a really dark one well like I will and I really also want to do some more paranormal things
But I just don't know how people are gonna candle that I don't know
How they handle everything go to bed gotta break out the candles and shut the lights. Oh
You don't have to tell me how to do it
Like I know how to do it. I just like it's weird thing to present to people, you know what I mean
Well, just the title of the stream dog Carol or something they'll know going in
No, I mean like the paranormal stuff, too
Like no everything all of it like it's like paranormal investigation shit all that stuff. I
Love that shit
You gonna abandon the mental hospitals around there?
We can we have I've so we don't have to go to an abandoned mental hospital or a cemetery to see fucking ghosts y'all
anywhere
Yeah, it's like a thing. They're everywhere. It's residual energy. They're with us. They're everywhere. Everything's all around
We're all portals by the way, we know TV's fucking shit. There's so much shit going on mirrors us
Anything that has a good reflection, you know what I mean? Like glass it's portals. We're portals especially for empathic
You know, you can have residual energy so there can be like an ex what do you call them a?
significant historical
moment or or
or
Circumstance or thing like it's a war or whatever is this residual energy and absolutely everything right?
Well, I'm sure I'm sure it hits differently if you go into a Tim Horton's or if you go into a cemetery
Well, no for sure
But it also hit you different like a cemetery is not the most haunted place
And you know people are like, oh, I'll go here no one best to get there
And like so much stuff on the internet and so much stuff in movies and obviously it's all fucking some of it's like fake but
That's where I like I love certain paranormal investigators that I'm subscribed to that are like I can see that I can see
I know that that's there right because there's lots of shit people are just making hype. They're just fucking setting stuff up, right?
There's a lot of fake shit on TV
I don't watch those TV shows. No, I don't really either
The EV you believe in the EVP stuff I kind of believe in that the ones on TV. I don't believe those
Well, yeah, so like E.B.P. that's just like electro. What is it electro?
It's like something yes electro voice
Projection electro. Yeah, something like that. So anyways E.B.P. and like s to Smith it all that stuff like so I am a freak
I'm a frequency. I am a channel, right?
So I vibe on that level so I'm always hearing that so for me. It's really not
unusual I guess for other people it's like super exciting and you know what spirit has a different
way to connect to everybody and it's how they want to present themselves in the way that they're
able to connect to communicate you know sometimes it's your fucking light sometimes it's this sometimes
it's that um there's like there's so much depth to it but I should do a whole segment on it honestly
that's cool if you can see the auras
I don't see or it like literally see like I see everything like sometimes it's like they'll present themselves to me
They'll be like, you know if they're in a car accident or something tragic happens and they have an acceptor understand
What's going on yet?
So they don't have the ability to choose their best self that they would like to be is that make sense because sometimes
Yeah, they can be a little girl, but they're not a little girl. It's that was a happy time for them replace it
they were most comfortable representing themselves or if they felt best about themselves, right?
So they have the ability to show us what they want to and present themselves how they want to.
Sometimes they come to me mangled in a car accident and I'm like I don't want to see that
shit so then I have had to my whole life learn how to filter that out kind of or say
when you're healed a little bit more or if I could help you heal to the point where you don't
present yourself like that because it's frightening, right?
It's not like they can help it, but it can be terrifying it's fucking terrifying and I'm
34 years old and I'm not scared of much but like sometimes
The darkness crawls out too and I can see that like I see it all the good the bad in between
They confused the scare the loss to fucking happy the you know what I mean like there's all of it
So it's just it all comes together. It must be hard to filter all that through
Well, that's why I drink
Now what's her name was saying she has it to Jamie says she has a little of a something like that going on too
Where she can she said she had gifts so she didn't elaborate on what she had
Yeah, like I worked with her
Quite a bitch and like opened her up to that a bit
So and yes, she's gifted but I mean it's a matter of what you hone in on right and just how what you nourish what you
It's just some it's a journey. We'll just say that
Yeah, and you know what even you come into things or like later in life than earlier sometimes like not everybody's
Wakes born like this and knows right away
Sometimes it comes later in your life, but it's experiences like our intuitions obviously always there right everybody's intuitive
Okay, everybody has empathy and compassion and all these things and lots of people are gifted and don't know they're gifted because it's never been
Encouraged or it's been conditioned or there's been like it's been bad. It's just been
given a bad rep or bad taste in their mouth you know what I mean or being evil or whatever this and that
but like if you okay so our soul plants the seeds and it's up to us to water and nourish the flowers of
the weeds and I feel like it's both you know what I mean because weeds have great properties look at
dandelions also the flowers do too you know what I mean so you can shut things down and you can open
This is that energy flowing through everything
Mm-hmm, and we all are on the same frequency in the same vibe, right? It's just sometimes
We're at different like
Levels and it's a matter of
Well, you know what we're all just at our different levels and we all are very unique
Like we can all have some of us have the same gift and like it
We just a different unique way of perception or the way that you
Deliver the message or the way that you intake the information. You know what I mean or that? Yeah, that's it
That's all it is. I'm gonna be a unique flair, right? No one's better than anyone else
Once you open yourself to these things then you're more in tune with everything. It's being susceptible to these things. Yes. Yeah, absolutely
There's too many people that they just want to laugh at it and be like, oh, it's bullshit
But they don't want to open themselves up to it
Well, they're just not ready yet
And then you know what once you realize your third eye is not your butthole is your fucking you'll get there
I don't know. Well, lots of people just aren't meant for it either
There's some space fillers, you know what I mean? And there's some people who are just meant to do
Different jobs in this world does that make sense and everybody has and plays a part and their energy and what they do like in and their physical job
But everybody plays a part and you can't be
That's why I don't get so fucking upset when people are like who is person said this about you and this person
So thinks that and this and that it's like well, okay. That's fine. I can't control that number one number two
It only has power if I give it power or they give it you know what I mean if I allow it to and
third
It's a matter of like if you know who you are and you know, things can't hurt you the way that
People think that they can because it's like I don't I'm not gonna allow it
And also like be neutral. It's like I don't
I'm not just sitting here like trying to be all nice all the time. Okay, you guys
It's just with the gifts that I have or the abilities whatever you want to call them. I am not
Allowed to not look at things from all aspects and sides. You know what I mean?
If someone's being a dickhead sometimes they're just fucking they have not had a good experience in some way or another
It's a trigger. You know what I mean?
Or it's an unhealed emotion or an unhealed trauma of sorts. It comes from somewhere. Everything comes from somewhere
Something somebody wakes up and they're just like I'm an asshole
You know, they're just like it comes from pain it comes from things and you have to understand that so I see through it's from all sides
But I think most of us do it's just um
The odd one that's, the odd one out every once in a while is because it's got no perspective or open-mindedness like you said, right?
I feel like all people have a purpose in our lives even negative
Everybody for whatever reason they're in your life, we're however long they're in your life. Yes. It's just like you said
Yeah, you just gotta know how to
No, there's no accident
Everything is well accidents. Yes, sorry, that was the wrong word
Accidents are accidents, but like there's things that are just fucking
Written for us. It's a path that we're supposed to follow whether we
fighting against it too is yeah exactly the contract that we signed before we
come down here. Now you'll have a better life when you just accept that and just
keep flowing through. Right and it's okay to be open-minded it's okay to believe
in what you believe in and it's okay to also be you know open to
Open to all the possibilities because like I said before the universe only knows one answer. Yes
So if we're always manifesting negative things or thinking native things about ourselves and
Projecting that as well, then that's what we're gonna get but we're feeding that source source feeds us
It's all just kind of a recycled thing, right?
Why look at everything like a test page everything to me in life is a test. Oh, absolutely. You're right 100%
I tell everybody this I'm like, you know God's testing you or the universe is testing you and
in certain ways just to see how you can react and how you can just evolve over time.
Well, exactly. And just when you think that you're healed from something fully,
that's exactly when that just starts to happen, especially.
It's like the universe is going to make sure that you know that that's not what you want anymore.
That's what you do want. Does that make sense?
Yeah, totally.
Yes. So it's always going to put that.
And as soon as you start to pull away from something that's had to hold on you for a long time,
And you're trying to ascend and move up and level up and just kind of be a
Different version of yourself and like actually settle into that
It's um the old you and the old lower vibrational energies and all of it that's attached is definitely going to
It's like are you are you ready for this or not? It's kind of like that test
You know what I mean? It's like oh well you think you're ready
So let's see if you can handle it if you go back to your old ways, then you're not ready for it, right?
That's that's what I tell people that are depressed, you know, they're very depressed and maybe they're suicidal every day's a new day
Yeah, you know, it's up to you to take that
Restart of a new day when you wake up in the morning and you you have the choice to do whatever you want with your life
You could change your whole outlook on life. You can change your whole aspect and just do something new
You know, you're unhappy
With your job get a new fucking job
You're unhappy with your family leave your fucking family go find a new one
Just you have the power to change your life into what you want to make it. It's gonna be hard
It's nothing's easy in life. If you want it bad enough, but you got to do it
And if you can do it to what you really want to make it happen in your life, then that's the best thing
There's no reason to just sit there and cry. Oh my life sucks. Oh, I want to die. I want to die. No, there's no point in that
Go and create the life that you want and if you fail in that then go make the choice of whatever you want to do
But at least go and try to change your life. How you want it to be
And don't say that I'm stuck doing what I'm doing all the only people that are stuck in doing what they're doing in life of
people in prison
All the rest of us we have a choice to do what we want in this world
For good or for bad
Yeah
Anyways, I
Probably should not be up here because I'm not really making anybody in here very fucking happy right now
Sorry
And normally it doesn't bother me, but like I don't know like you know fucking
Like you come to my fucking lives like half the people two of them some of them are mods on my channel
And they come to mine, and it's like oh nothing. It's like they didn't fucking never mind
And you want to talk to me about being fake and no, I don't think I'm the sixth sense girl a kid or whatever
That's retarded
I just like I see things differently
And you know what if you've ever come to my channel or if you've ever experienced any kind of interaction with me when it comes to
You know that that shit and also don't just fucking shuffle cards, dude. That's ridiculous. It's not an ability
I know that anyone can shuffle cards. It's
Anyways, I don't have to explain myself. Yeah, man. They're just trying to get a rise out of you, dude
Don't say that bullshit
Read all the good stuff
There's good stuff look what that Marcy's writing she wrote a whole paragraph about some kind of civilization and well Marcy's yeah
Wonderful though. She's and Liz is there with her positive amazing for sure. Yeah
So I always always sort out the good, you know if you guys if it's not for you
Then why do a lot of you come to my channel when I'm live and and you know and most just come and take just you
Why do you come there like I don't get it?
They want to get a rise out of you, that's all
Well, I'd like to see what some of you do and I'd love to meet you guys personally because like, you know
I go up I cam up not that I'm not glorifying it. I'm just saying
If I'm fake then why am I one of the more real ones on here?
I'm not scared. I get cam up. I'm always the same. You know what I mean? I'm not not
Hiding things. It's ridiculous. It's ridiculous
If you're gonna judge give me something to judge make it fair, you know
They will always judge. We don't have to listen. No one judges me. God is the final judge.
Yeah, it is. It's very noisy over here.
Just sitting by the brook
Marcia, are you a troll?
Are you trolling me?
Liz, of course, it's not a recording. What do you mean, I'm outside. I'm just chilling.
This is Spunky's dog, by the way. I saw this picture. She had a dog on the other day. He
Always knew your horny broad
That is a cute dog she has a couple of cute dogs she just lost one though. Oh sad
Okay, so what's the name of that kid that used to do the psychic readings you remember him
And he was accused of fraud
He's like a young kind of dude and looked weird. Yeah, I think he had blonde hair
Looked on his name
Like a real person or like a movie. What do you know? No, this is a real person
Somebody just mentioned that dot true calling. I was out that it just made me think of that kid
He used to be on TV can he look kind of gay and he used to always be on dr. Phil and stuff like that
I don't know if you remember that
Was it like Matthew the medium no no he was um he was trying to um
He used to help the um celebrities a lot used to be with celebrities
Oh, but
What's his name?
Can't think of his name. He was always around for like the longest time then all of a sudden he just disappeared
I'm not sure. I will have to i'm thinking about it. It's all in the tip of my tongue. Um
Fuck you know his face, you know, I'm thinking I do I do but I can't remember his name. I thought it was math like
Something something Matthew the medium no, it's not it. I used to do the readings and everybody would be like oh, yeah
But you could tell it was like something phony about the whole thing. It was just like this is like some Hollywood shit. This is crazy
Of course, you know, I'm one of those people that I don't really believe until it's something that
really resonates with me
Like the few rings you've done for me, they usually you usually post something out that like yeah, yeah that resonates
Well, that's good, you know, that's why that's why I buy into it when I test myself to it's not like I just I'm like I'm obviously
You know, I test I test these abilities or whatever the fuck you want to call them as well
I'm very logical. I'm also spiritual and like there's you know room for both of those things within all of us
But at the same time, it's like, you know, I'm not skeptical of myself. I'm just saying I always test it too
You know, I always want to make sure it's it's accurate or correct
And also it takes a lot to to say these things to people it takes a lot of energy to like just
To do this you guys it's not like I'm just doing it because I fucking want to be cool like this is just how it is
No, you did a reading for boy yesterday. It was very thorough and very
Very specific to what he was, uh, you know getting out of it and it was great
I'm like, wow, she's putting a lot of cards and reading into this. It was fantastic
Well, exactly and it's again later on he really appreciate that really yeah, he did like that a lot
That's good
So I don't have to go to the nut house quite yet
No, I appreciate you guys you and psyche psyche is great with his
Yeah, I try not to I try not to eat up time
That's why I only asked for like one card when I do it because you know, I know he's doing he has to do is a
Whole thing with cash apps and stuff like that. So I don't want to eat up this whole time with a whole bunch of cards
But I appreciate it from you guys. It's great
Not Sylvia Brown. No, she died, didn't she?
Sylvia Brown used to be the one who used to say she'd know where the kidnapped kids were and stuff like that.
I remember her.
She used to work with the police, I think.
They tried to debunk her. I think they said she was a fraud too. I'm not sure what happened in the end.
Is I'm not anyways. I'm not doing this to be like I'm not trying to trick you guys would be a fraud or take your money
Or anything stupid like that. I'm just just be myself. I don't know
And I'm just a person just like everybody else and going through shit and I just its experiences and it's you know
Sometimes isn't it nice to just
Feel like somebody gets you
Without knowing you
Yeah, no you have a lot of fun around here. That's the best thing
And when you do these things for people, it's like it really connects with them emotionally
People really appreciate that and all the negative people man, just you know to do with that shit just block it out
I know it's hard, but
Just laugh at it
I got people here saying I got no legs for Christ's sake page come on. What am I supposed to react to that?
They say you have no legs like Lieutenant Dan. Yeah, I got no legs
Yeah, I'm hobbling everywhere. I'm walking around with my arms
Hey Jamie, good morning
What about me Marcia? What about me? Give me a little love. What the fuck?
Jamie are you talking about like there's other people in here that are really me because
Marcy and Gotti, there's certain people that certainly have been mean. I think it's-
Is she saying that? She's not saying that about us is she?
She's saying don't be mean to my friends which is like you know the people she mentioned.
Did she just throw us in there with the rest of them? I thought she was being complimentary. I
Guess I should read these things before I say anything
Just woke up and saw this bullshit and Rewound a little bit and went what the fuck page is incredible
Godie Marcy Liz and you guys are really rude leave my friends alone. Okay, I
Think she's come to sit with you
page
No
Think no, I think she means well. She's she obviously means well
She I think she means like you guys doesn't mean that you guys are being real
I think there's people in the chat that are being rude
You was saying hi she was saying hi to them, okay
Yeah, exactly we're good. That's I thought I
Love you Marzino. I'm happy to give you a reading soon rather than later here. You've been waiting for a while
Well, you're not even waiting, but like I know you've wanted one for a while
Well, it would look otherwise shaggy
Topics what should we talk about? What do you want to talk about? I don't know not
Negativity and shit. I don't care actually. I don't even care anymore. I'm late. What's your favorite horror movies page?
Do you like horror movies? Okay, so listen up. Yeah, I actually just watched this one and nothing has freaked me out in a long time
But hell house. I just watched that
it's a real documentary about this hotel and
These people that go in there and they either rented or have some rights or some sort of rights to it and
There's actual footage and everything and they go in and they try to make it a haunted house
And there's like one and two and three so people keep doing this even after this first fucking crazy video
Um and the experience and whatever obviously people are you know, they're going there in there for that
But they set up a haunted house. Um, just go watch that you guys it's it's crazy if you like documentary
It's like a real real type of thing. It'll fuck you up. Yeah, and I honestly I like stuff like that
I mean it doesn't really scare me. I see it all the time, but it's that one
I don't know. It's just it's a good one. It'll it'll get you going
Yeah, I don't like that gore shit
No, it's not like gory slasher film or cheesy. It's like fucking like actual real like hauntings and shit
Yeah, like spine tingling shit like that. Yeah, me too like stuff. It's real
Because it's real right like it happens in the world that that makes it worse
Well, it makes it much more spooky because it's connected to the reality. Yeah, I need a little supernatural in there
I need something that's gonna be like
The paranormal the supernatural it's like, you know
The real good little spooky shit that the real shit
Not like that just like cheesy slasher gore film fucking
Like what is that one terrifier? I don't know. That's an example. I haven't seen that yet. I gotta see that
I heard it's pretty good. Well, yeah, I'm sorry when I say when I say gore. I mean like that, um
This human centipede shit. Okay. Well, like, you know, I feel like that's creepy fucking shit
I don't like exactly what I'm talking about like that stuff's just like cooked
Yeah, I don't mind. I like it. I like a good Friday 13th where he's killing everybody. I like that
But I don't like the like super creepy weirdo shit
Like the first time the first saw was really good
Maybe the second one, but then when they once they got to like four and five
They just started doing it just to like slice up people's faces and stuff like that thought to be too much
Why am I having a pre-menopausal episode or is that a scary movie like what is what do you talk about Joe?
Is this Joe Shippley?
Who's Joe Joe 2.0 is the same person, right?
That's a fake Joe. It's a fake Joe
right, so
Who else is fake in here?
The fake
Everybody except for Slayer Marcy and Liz and Jamie. That's it
This is the real Beetlejuice you like everybody else is a fake. Well, Yumi's not
I don't know
Is a weird fucking weird shit on on in here. Yeah, we see that movie Halloween 3
Yeah
With the druids and stuff like that they make robots out of these fucking
This dude makes robots. He takes over the town and then he wants to give these masks to the kid
They have like a little thing on the back and they watch this commercial. You ever see that one?
And the thing creates like a laser beam it goes through their head and
All these creatures start coming out of their bodies and stuff like that
You ever see that one? That's a good one. I have, yep
Jim you're fake you're the fakest one of all. What do you mean? I'm not fake. I
Never believe a word you say Jim
Yeah, I've seen those I've seen those both and they're all right. I like
The nun was good. It was creepy, but it's that's based on the what's it called the
Conjuring isn't it the Conjuring and then
It was just another good one. You know what movie I don't like it freaked me out. It just still freaks me out is like
the descent
Descent which one was that were they going to the cave? Yes, I don't like that like who also who does like I don't know
It's a cool feel like to go into confined spaces and caves and stuff like I just couldn't I can't
Clostrophobia is a thing for me. It's like big fear. Yeah going into caves is fine
But once they go into those little crevices and shit like that. What the fuck you doing?
Right and like people who are like up like adapt to the living in there and just like
One guy got stuck going into one of those things and he just died there. Yeah, I know it's terrible. It's what the fuck
I want to think about that process of death. That's like okay. I'm not scared to die
But I think that that's the thing like people it's not death we fear
It's like the way that we go that we think about you know
I mean there's a process we put our minds through just like stress and anxiety that like everything else in life
But that's obviously bigger. It's just it's it's what's in our mind or how we think we're gonna go the process of death not death itself
No the dying part death is fine, but the dying
That's not cool how you die
Let's paint the better
Now they say once you die it's quick, but depends on how long it takes
That's why it's always best to die in your sleep
Let them worry about it in the morning
Well, there's some caves are okay. Yeah, I know that I'm just like that movie freaked me out
It's not the concept of just caves all around
but um, I
Don't know so what was the scariest movie that you guys have ever watched like what one just like freaks you right out
Like where you honestly couldn't be an adult about it or sleep
For me
for you and the chat
scariest movie for me um
You know really freaked me out. I don't know if I was scared or what but it really like unnerved me was that a
Blair witch project. It was stupid. It was a stupid movie, but it's just the shit that happened at the end
It was like so weird
Like what the fuck I know I knew it was all fake and stuff like that, but it's just the way they presented it
Ended like a very unnerving way
You ever see it the one with the camera? It's all shaky. Oh, yeah, of course
Do you ever see like well anything like that where it's like the real it's real documented stuff? It's hard to it's hard to
Question it, you know if it's not staged
Then that's real and that's scary I
Hate movies where like kids are the killers
Well, women are the killers. I'm like, nah, I don't want to watch that.
Okay, what's going on, Jamie? What's the matter? What is happening? What did I miss here?
What happened? I don't know.
Two girls one cup. I love that one. It's one of my favorites
Gross
Are you sorry?
No, I did not but I've heard enough about it. I don't ever need to see it. I've heard enough about it. I
Started recently like a couple weeks ago. I'm like what the fuck this this shit still holds up
Jamie that's not a nice thing to say Beetlejuice. This can't be the real build like this can't be the Beetlejuice we know
Maybe I don't know she's a lesbian. I don't even know she's a lesbian. That's fine
Even if she is it doesn't matter, but like I don't think she is so
I don't think Beetlejuice had ever seen anything like that about Jamie, but I don't know
Hold on Macaw
The two girls one cup you would say that
That's not me I don't have a bird that's definitely for God is
My seven let's you die Marcy. I'm always protecting you Marcy. Don't worry
Notice Shaggy left and now Vader came back
What does that mean dough like what oh?
My gosh, all right, well, I don't know I don't not dig in this fucking chat, so I might leave
He's calling it racially charged
No, I know I'm just like there's other comments and shit. I'm just not
Sometimes I just want to come up here and like
Us enjoying each other's company, which probably will never fucking happen, but
Without the chat, oh, it's never gonna happen. Yeah, you're right. It would probably happen in your like on your stream
You'll have nestle get negativity over there
Who's devil eyes
I need like a guidebook for this shit.
Paige, just start some drama, you ready?
Let's send some pizzas to somebody.
Whose address do you got?
Who wants a pizza?
Whoever wants a pizza sent to their house, press 2.
Not you you means you can't send pizza to my house. I live way to have in the middle of nowhere
There's no delivery. There's no delivery available ever anywhere. We'll find some sucker driver to deliver it
There's a talking Rob. I want to be six foot seven like him and very muscular. I'm looking very feminine in my pic
Well, you want pizza you press one you me sorry it was two no pizza for you
Have you ever had a breakfast pizza with eggs and bacon I think so I
Had
Like eggs Benedict's pizza one time, but like I made it. It was amazing
That's the one with the tomatoes, right? No, it's eggs egg. So hollandaise sauce and
approached eggs and you can do
Well, there's a you know a whole process to it
You just make it you never had all like eggs benedicts. I've been okay. You can put tomatoes on you put whatever you want on it
But is that the shit that's like runny egg? I don't eat runny egg
I just have you can have a soft hard or medium egg
But you can have it's with holiday sauce on an English muffin. Yeah, I know holiday sauce. No, it's too fancy for me
I'm a ketchup and scrambled eggs kind of guy
Little cheese some peppers good
Well, Christine makes a great breakfast pizza.
chorizo isn't that like sausage
christian you're telling god to widen his horizons
i suppose i should eat caviar too right
Good morning Christine
Did they knock can you holy shit
Well, Marcia got an arcant.
That's rough.
Epidural.
Holy shit.
Vader, I think he's asleep.
Psyche, Vader's backstage.
Oh, there he is.
Woo!
Let's go!
Vader, what up, man?
Yeah, baby!
What are you doing, Vader?
Woo!
Vader, what are you doing, bro?
Vader.
Vader, what are you doing?
Hey, that's not Vader.
I don't think that's Vader.
Oh, shit.
Tell me a course that's not.
I don't think that's Vader.